♪♪
Tim Cook: 早上好欢迎参加 WWDC
Tim Cook: Good morning, and welcome to WWDC
今天是个重要的日子
We have a big day of announcements
我们将和大家分享一系列最新的技术和平台
about our latest technologies and platforms
这一系列平台及其驱动的各类产品
These platforms, and the products they drive
给我们用户提供奇妙的体验
deliver amazing experiences for our users
也为广大开发者们带来各种意想不到的机会
and provide developers with incredible opportunities
让大家得以充分发挥自己的超能力
so they can use their superpowers to innovate, create
来不断创新、创造并共同协作
打造出各类 app 持续改变我们的世界
and collaborate, making apps that continue to change the world
WWDC 旨在为这个社群提供所需
And WWDC is designed to give this community
帮助大家完成自己的杰作
what they need to do their very best work
我们也积极地在 WWDC 之外支持着开发者们
We love to support our developers beyond WWDC
包括全方位的顶级支持和一系列重要的项目
with comprehensive world-class support and other important initiatives
我们刚刚落成了全新的 Developer Center
We just opened our brand-new Developers Center across from Apple Park
就在 Apple Park 对面
便于开发者们和我们的工程师交流沟通
where developers can engage with our engineers
为了接触全球的开发者社群
And to reach our global community
去年秋季我们首次推出了各种线上 Tech Talks
this past fall we introduced our first online Tech Talks for developers
让开发者们学习我们最新的技术
to learn more about our new technologies
并通过现场讲座和一对一交流直接和 Apple 工程师进行探讨
and directly connect with Apple engineers
in live sessions and one-on-one office hours
我们也致力于培养新一代开发者
We are also committed to cultivating the next generation of developers
包括各项旨在帮助少数族裔的举措
including efforts to reach underrepresented communities
因此我们的 Developer Academy
So our developer academies teach students the fundamentals of coding
不仅会教导学生们编程的基础
还会教授各项必要技能
as well as the other necessary skills
以帮助他们在 app 相关行业中寻找和创造就业机会
to find and create jobs in the app economy
全球共有 17 所
There are 17 around the world
包括我们去年十月在底特律成立的 Academy
including the academy in Detroit we founded in October
是 Apple Racial Equity and Justice Initiative 的一部分
as a part of Apple's Racial Equity and Justice Initiative
然后在沙特
And in Saudi Arabia, we launched our first developer academy for women in February
我们在二月创立了首个为女性开发者服务的 Academy
我们的 Entrepreneur Camps 为少数族裔的开发者们
Our Entrepreneur Camps provide developers from underrepresented communities
提供了来自 Apple 的指导、灵感启发以及洞察分析
with mentorship, inspiration, and insights from Apple
最开始一系列的 Entrepreneur Camps 主要针对女性开发者
The first camps were for female founders, and this past year
而在去年我们进一步开放给黑人和拉丁裔创业者
we expanded the camps to reach Black and Latin founders
学员们借此机会获得了至关重要的启动资金
Alumni have gone on to secure major funding
并通过 App Store 获得成功
and see great success on the App Store
这些持续的努力赋予所有开发者们
These ongoing efforts empower all developers with the tools
用来改变世界的工具、技术以及灵感启发
technologies, and inspiration to change the world for the better
数百万开发者参与了去年的 WWDC
Last year, many millions of developers engaged in WWDC
而今年我们期待将迎来更多参与者
and we expect millions more to join us again this year
事实上我们非常荣幸地向大家宣布
In fact, we're excited to say we've grown our developer community
整个 Apple 开发者社群已有超过 3400 万人
to over 34 million Apple developers
接下来的一个星期令人充满期待
We have a huge week ahead of us, with an amazing online experience
有各种精彩的在线活动
包括各类讲座、实验室和在线聊天室
including sessions, labs, and digital lounges
都将免费向开发者们开放
which will all be available for free to our developers
Today, we're going to push our platforms further than ever
今天我们的各个平台将迎来全新篇章
进一步赋能广大开发者和我们的用户
for our developers and our users
让我们直入主题有请 Craig
So let's get started by sending it over to Craig
♪♪
Craig Federighi: 我非常兴奋和大家分享今天的内容
Craig Federighi: I'm really excited about what we have to show you today
不过呢让我们先下个楼
But first, let's head downstairs
♪♪
现在让我们来聊聊 iOS
Now, let's talk about iOS
iPhone 和 iOS 二者相互结合让你事半功倍
Together with iPhone, iOS helps you get so much done
无论在家或是在外
whether you're at home or on the move
下一个版本也就是 iOS 16
And the next release, iOS 16, offers new intelligence
将带来各类全新的智能技术、共享和交流功能
sharing, and communication features that are going to enhance
将大大优化提升你通过 iPhone 来完成的事
so much of what you do with your iPhone
与此同时还将有一系列全新卓越的个性化功能
And those come together with an incredible set of new personalization features
给你带来耳目一新且专属于你的使用体验
that will make your experience feel fresh and completely you
让我们先从全新的锁定屏幕说起
Let's get started with the all-new Lock Screen
每当拿起 iPhone 最先看到的就是锁定屏幕
The Lock Screen is the first thing you see every time you pick up your iPhone
你能在这里查看日期和时间
It's a place where you can check the date and time
一览重要信息
look out for key messages
启动相机来快速捕捉精彩瞬间
and launch the camera to quickly capture the moment
这也属于个性化空间
And it's just as much a place for personalization
大家都会在锁定屏幕上放一张照片
where so many of you put a photo that makes iPhone uniquely yours
让 iPhone 一看就是你的
在 iOS 16 我们为锁定屏幕带来了有史以来最大的更新
In iOS 16, we're bringing the biggest update ever to the Lock Screen
彻底重新构建了其外观和功能
completely reimagining how it looks and works for you
让我们看看
Let's take a look
♪♪
新的锁定屏幕保留了 iPhone 的风格
Craig: The new Lock Screen remains undeniably iPhone
但同时提供给你全新方式
while also giving you new ways to make it more personal
使其更个人化、更美观、更有帮助
beautiful, and helpful than ever
让我来展示一下
Let me show you
这是我的锁定屏幕
Here's my Lock Screen
你会注意到微妙的景深效果
You'll notice the subtle depth effect
我女儿的照片呈现在时间显示的前面
with my daughters appearing in front of the time
我很喜欢这样的效果
I really love it
然后我只需长按就可以继续进行个性化设置
Now, if I just press and hold, I can personalize it further
这样轻点自定就可以开始编辑了
I'll just tap Customize, and now I'm in the editor
你看
Now, check this out
我只需轻扫就可以尝试不同的风格
I can simply swipe to try out different styles
色彩、背景和时间字型会自动更改
that automatically change the color filter, the background
相互呼应
and the font for the time, all to complement each other
这样真好看
These look really beautiful
就这么定吧！
So let's go with this one
当然如果我改变任何一个细节
Now, of course, if I want to change anything
很容易就可以进一步调整成我想要的样子
it's easy to dial it in further to get it just the way I want it
我可以轻点锁定屏幕上的任何元素
All I need to do is tap on any element of the Lock Screen to start editing
直接进行编辑
让我来自定义字型
So let's customize the font
我可以尝试不同的字体
I can audition different typefaces
还有不同的颜色
and choose from different colors
我喜欢这个颜色
And I like this color. I'll just adjust the shade a little bit
让我来调整一下色度
现在看起来真棒
I think this looks awesome now
我还可以在锁定屏幕上添加小组件来增加实用性
Now, I can also make my Lock Screen more helpful
by putting widgets right on the Lock Screen
让我把女儿的照片往下移一点
So let me move the girls down here
再轻点进入小组件库
and tap in to bring up the widget gallery
这些可以让你一览无余各类信息
And these are really useful for getting information at a glance
比如日历上的下一个日程
like upcoming calendar events
让我来加上气温
So I'll add the temperature
我的健身记录圆环
my Activity rings, and let's drag in the calendar widget
再拖入日历小组件
这看起来棒极了
Now, this is great
更棒的是锁定屏幕可以不止一个
And what's even better is, I'm not limited to just one
让我来再创建一个
Let's create another
我可以调出全新的锁定屏幕图库
I can bring up our brand-new wallpaper gallery
这里展示了一些选择为你提供灵感
which showcases a bunch of options for inspiration
可选的真的超多
And there are plenty to choose from here
有数以百万的组合让你充分进行个性化设置
So much room for personalization, with millions of combinations
照片随机显示功能
With Photo Shuffle, I can choose a set of photos to shuffle throughout the day
让我可以选一组照片在一天里随机滚动显示
另外还有建议照片都是从我的个人图库中精选出的
And we also have Suggested Photos
intelligently curated from my personal library
例如为家人拍的最棒的照片
like the best shots of family that look great on the Lock Screen
放在锁定屏幕上就很合适
这张很好看可以添加到我的精选里
Now, this is an awesome one to add to my collection
我已经有好多不同的锁定屏幕了
Now, I've created a bunch of other Lock Screens
只需轻扫就可以任意更换
and by simply swiping, I can switch between them
你可以发挥创意的空间非常大
It's amazing the range you can create
这是天气可以显示实时天气状况
Here's Weather, which shows live weather conditions
例如倾盆大雨甚至还有闪电
like a downpour and lightning
我很喜欢这个动画
I just love this animation
这边有一个很酷的表情符号墙纸
Here's a really cool emoji wallpaper
还有我们的彩虹墙纸
and our Pride wallpaper
这是我们的天文精选中的一个
And here's one from our Astronomy collection
注意看这个流畅的动画跟着我轻扫进入主屏幕
Watch how it animates fluidly as I swipe into the Home Screen
太酷了
So cool
这就是全新的锁定屏幕简介
So that's a quick look at the all-new Lock Screen
开发者们也可以利用 WidgetKit
And for developers, WidgetKit makes it quick and easy
快速轻松地将 app 的信息概览放在锁定屏幕上
to put glanceable information from their app here as well
全新的锁定屏幕非常美观
The new Lock Screen is so beautiful, we wanted to make sure
我们当然想你可以一直欣赏
即使在收到很多通知的时候
that you can always enjoy it, even if you get a lot of notifications
有时候通知会遮盖住锁定屏幕上你的个人照片
Sometimes, notifications can cover up your personal photo
所以我们重新构思了通知的出现方式
So we've rethought how they appear
现在当你收到通知时它们将在锁屏底部滚动显示
Notifications now roll in from the bottom of the Lock Screen as you receive them
当然你也可以选择将其隐藏起来
and you can choose to hide them throughout the day
有时候你会从某个 app 收到一连串的通知
Now, sometimes you get a bunch of notifications from an app
比如说你正在关注一场篮球赛的比分
like when you're following the score of a basketball game
现在呢有个更好的方法来追踪动态
Well, now there's a better way to keep tabs
那就是实时活动
with something called Live Activities
更便于你通过锁定屏幕实时跟进正在发生的动态
Live Activities make it easier to stay on top of things
that are happening in real time right from your Lock Screen
开发者们在今年晚些时候 iOS 16 的一次更新后
And for developers, starting in an update to iOS 16 later this year
可以通过实时活动 API
they can use the Live Activities API
来打造这些设计紧凑又一目了然的体验
to create these compact and glanceable experiences
这将方便用户关注 NBA 球赛
This will make it really easy to follow that NBA game
追踪 Uber 行程的进度
track the progress of an Uber ride
跟进个人锻炼情况等
see how you're doing on your workout, and more
同时不影响锁定屏幕上的其他元素显示
all while letting the other elements on the Lock Screen shine
我们当中很多人最爱做的就是听音乐
One of the most popular activities for many of us is listening to music
那现在有了实时活动
And now with Live Activities, the Now Playing controls can expand
“播放中”控件就可以延展到全屏视图
让你可以边听音乐边欣赏专辑封面
to a full screen view that celebrates album art while you listen along
这就是全新的锁定屏幕
So that's the all-new Lock Screen
这些更新同时带来了强大的新方式
There are some really powerful ways these updates tie together
和我们去年推出的专注模式相整合
and build upon what we introduced last year with Focus
专注模式帮助我们减少干扰并集中精力于当下
Focus has helped people reduce distractions and stay in the moment
今年我们进一步提升了专注模式
And this year, we're taking it further
首先就是将其带到了锁定屏幕
starting with extending Focus to your Lock Screen
这意味着你所选的照片和小组件
This means your choice of a photo and widgets
可以与某个特定的专注模式相互绑定
can all be tied to a particular Focus
现在既然可以有多个锁定屏幕
And now that you can have multiple Lock Screens
你可将它们和一天中不同的专注模式相匹配
you can match them to the appropriate Focus throughout your day
你可以为工作专注模式设置相应的锁定屏幕
You can have a dedicated one for when you're in a Work Focus
加上小组件来显示下一个会议日程或待完成事项清单
with widgets showing your upcoming meeting or to-do list
或者轻扫一下启动你的个人专注模式
Or, with just a swipe, you can activate your Personal Focus
你所有相应的通知设置也将同时应用
All of your corresponding notification settings apply
并启动相应的主屏幕
and it extends to your Home Screen too
你可以保留自己喜爱的常用 app 或小组件
So now you can elevate your favorite apps or widgets
与亲友保持联系
for keeping up with friends and family
现在你的专注模式也可应用于 app 层级
And now, your Focus can also carry into the apps themselves
利用专注模式过滤条件
with Focus filters, which let you filter out distracting content
减少令人分心的内容
比如说 Safari 浏览器
Let's take Safari, for example
与其看到你所有的网页
Instead of seeing all of your websites
你可以打开工作专注模式过滤条件
you can turn on the Work Focus filter and see only the tabs that relate to work
只保留和工作相关的标签页
除了 Safari 浏览器中的标签页组
And you can filter not just tab groups in Safari
你还可以过滤信息 app 中的某些对话
but also conversations in Messages, accounts in Mail, and events in Calendar
邮件 app 中的某些账户
以及日历 app 中的某些日程
我们为开发者提供了新的 API
And for developers, we have a new API
帮助你在使用他们开发的 app 时也能保持专注
so they can help you focus in their apps as well
这些专注模式的更新可以帮你来设定界限
These updates to Focus can help you draw boundaries
助你平衡生活中的各个时刻
and find balance throughout all of the moments in your life
现在让我们来聊聊信息 app 的新功能
Now, let's talk about what's in store for Messages
每天数以亿计的人依靠着信息 app
Hundreds of millions of people rely on Messages every single day
它成为了不可或缺的工具让我们和至亲挚爱保持联络
It's integral to how we communicate with the people who matter most
今天我们为信息 app 添加了三个呼声最高的新功能
And now, we're adding three of the most highly-requested features to Messages
首先你是不是有过发送消息后
First, have you ever sent a Message only to immediately realize
立即意识到没有准确表达你的意思？
you didn't quite say what you intended?
不用担心
Well, no worries
现在你可以编辑刚发送出去的信息
Because now you can edit any message you just sent
不必再担心令人尴尬的错别字
so embarrassing typos can be a thing of the past
其次你是不是有过其实根本不想发出去的信息？
Second, have you ever wished you'd never sent that message at all?
好消息！现在有了撤销发送功能
Well, good news–now you have undo send
你可以赶紧撤回刚才的失误
so you can immediately recall a recent misfire
最后你可以将对话标记为未读
And finally, you can now mark any thread as unread
尤其适合你当下没空回复
a perfect tool if you don't have time to respond in the moment
但又想待会查看的情况下
and want to be sure to come back to a message later
这三个功能将大大改变
These three features are going to make a big difference
你日常如何使用信息 app
in how you use Messages every single day
信息 app 不仅可以简单高效发送信息
Messages makes texting easy and efficient, and it's also a great way to share
还便于大家共享内容
去年我们推出了与你共享功能
Last year, we introduced Shared with You, which takes things like photos, links
朋友们在信息 app 与你分享的照片、链接、音乐
and music that your friends share with you in Messages and highlights them
会在相应的 app 中突出显示以便你回头去欣赏
right in the app where you'd like to enjoy them later
而我们很高兴推出新的 API 让开发者们可以调用与你共享
And for developers, we're really excited
to make Shared with You available with a new API
这样当有人给你发送有趣视频
So when someone sends you a funny video, a worthwhile article
值得一看的文章
或你当下没空查看的食谱
or a recipe that you don't have time to check out in the moment
下次你在开启相应的 app 时会出现在你眼前
it'll be there waiting for you the next time you open that app
而如果是实时与他人分享的话
And when it comes to sharing in real time with others, people are loving SharePlay
同播共享就是人们非常喜爱的功能
带来了独一无二的神奇体验
It's stellar for enjoying shared experiences
在 FaceTime 通话同时共享精彩内容
while connecting over FaceTime
比如一起追剧
Like watching TV shows, listening to music
一起听音乐
还有一起大汗淋漓地锻炼
or breaking a sweat to a synced up workout
许多大家常用的 app 都基于同播共享
So many of your favorite apps are using SharePlay
来创建共享体验
to create shared experiences
比如一起听 Better Sleep 的睡前故事
like listening to bedtime stories together with Better Sleep
或者在 Heads Up 一起畅玩游戏
or playing a rowdy game of Heads Up, no matter how far apart you are
不管你们相距多远
而今年
And this year, we're making it easier to discover
在 FaceTime 通话中也将更容易发现这些精彩的同播共享体验
all of these awesome SharePlay experiences from within your FaceTime call
只需轻点一下
With just a tap, you can jump into SharePlay-supported apps
就能找到手机上已经支持同播共享的 app
that you already have on your phone, or discover new experiences
或者发现可以和朋友们分享的新体验
that you can share with your friends
而为了让你有更多机会来共享体验
And to give you more opportunities to enjoy shared experiences
我们正把同播共享扩展到 FaceTime 通话之外
we're extending SharePlay beyond FaceTime and bringing it to Messages
将其带入信息 app 中！
这是来自开发者们的第一大要求
This was the number one request from developers
现在如果你有想分享的东西
Now when you find something you want to share
例如 Disney+ 的一部电影
你只需要在那里开启同播共享
like a movie on Disney+, you can kick off SharePlay right there
就能够一边看电影一边在信息 app 里聊天
and enjoy it together while chatting in Messages
不仅可以同步观看
You can watch in sync, and you've got the same instantaneous
播放控制也可实时同步
带来奇妙的同播共享体验
shared playback controls that make SharePlay magical
所以不管是要同播共享你每周的电影之夜
So whether you're using SharePlay for your weekly movie night
或是将信息标为未读以便稍后回复
or marking a message unread so you can respond later
信息 app 能满足你各种需求让你轻松保持联系
Messages has everything you need to connect with ease
此外编写信息也更方便了
And we're making it that much easier to compose Messages
这归功于听写功能的一些更新
with some updates to Dictation
下面有请 Robby 来给你分享
To tell you more, here's Robby
Robby Walker: 通过听写你只需动口就能输入文字
Robby Walker: Dictation lets you type just by speaking
可以比用键盘打字更快
and can be much faster than typing with the Keyboard
所以它常用来做记录、发信息等
This is why it's so popular for taking notes, sending messages, and more
事实上听写功能使用频次每个月超过 180 亿
In fact, Dictation is used over 18 billion times each month
同时这一功能在设计上已将隐私保护考虑其中
And it's designed to protect your privacy
多亏神经网络引擎听写可以完全在设备端运行
Thanks to the Neural Engine, Dictation can happen entirely on-device
今天我们很高兴带来全新的设备端听写体验
Today, we're excited to introduce an all-new on-device Dictation experience
让你在语音和触控之间流畅切换
that lets you fluidly move between voice and touch
让我们来看看
Let's take a look
我将用新的听写功能来发送这封邮件
We'll use our new dictation experience to send an email
现在当我使用听写功能的同时键盘也保持启用
Now, when I start dictating, the keyboard stays open
这样我可以在语音和触控输入间自由切换
so I can switch between using voice and touch
我甚至可以用触控选择文本
I can even select text using touch and replace it with my voice
然后用语音进行替换
只需动口即可
Just by speaking
你在编辑一段较长的信息吗
Are you sending a longer message?
听写能自动在文字里加入标点符号
Dictation automatically adds punctuation to the text
好酷爆炸头表情符号
"That's so cool! Mind blown emoji!"
当你用 Siri 发送消息时也可自动添加标点符号和听写表情符号
Automatic punctuation and emoji dictation also work
when you send messages with Siri
而今年要在其他 app 里使用 Siri 也变得更方便了
And this year, we're making it easier to use Siri with apps
目前有超过 15000 个 app 可与 Siri 配合使用
There are over 15,000 apps that work with Siri
都是基于 SiriKit 和 Siri 快捷指令
using SiriKit and Siri Shortcuts
目前为止许多操控仍需要手动设置
And today, these require manual setup
所以我们推出了一个新的开发者 API
So we're introducing a new developer API
由 Swift 编码语言编写称之为 App Intents
built using the Swift programming language called App Intents
现在无需设置就可运行快捷指令
Now shortcuts work with zero setup
直接在所支持的各类 app 里靠 Siri 来完成任务
so you can use Siri to get things done with supported apps
现在让我们来谈谈另一个由智能技术驱动的功能
Now let's talk about another feature powered by intelligence: Live Text
实况文本
实况文本真的很有用
Live Text is so useful
因为它深入集成于整个操作系统中
because it's deeply integrated across the entire OS
让你能交互使用整个系统里图片中的文字
letting you interact with text in images across the system
不管是相机 app、Safari 浏览器
from Camera and Safari to Notes and Screenshots
备忘录 app 甚至是截屏中
今年我们很高兴将这样的深度集成更进一步
And this year, we're excited to take this integration further
将实况文本带到视频里！
by bringing Live Text to video
现在你可以在任何帧暂停视频
Now you can pause a video on any frame and interact with text
交互使用里面的文字
就像之前在照片里那样
just like you can today with photos
比如直接在编程视频里复制代码示例
It's great for copying code samples
我们还增加了一些基于实况文本的快速操作
We're also accelerating the things you do with Live Text with quick actions
例如只需要轻点一下
So now you're just a tap away from converting currency
来换算汇率或者翻译外文
and translating a foreign language
若要更丰富的翻译体验
And for an even richer translation experience
可以调用翻译 app 中的新相机视图使用实况文本
you'll be able to use Live Text while in the Translate app
with our new camera view
这尤其适用于有大量文本需要翻译的时候
This will be great for when you have lots of text to translate
而我们也很高兴为开发者带来实况文本 API
And for developers, we're also excited to announce a Live Text API
很快你就可以直接在 Vimeo 等 app 中从照片或视频截取文本
Soon you will be able to grab text straight from photos
and videos in apps like Vimeo
当然照片里远不止有文本
And photos are about more than just text
所以我们去年推出了 Visual Look Up 这个功能
That's why last year we introduced Visual Look Up
用来识别如宠物、地标、植物等主体
a feature that recognizes objects like pets, landmarks, plants, and more
为你提供图片里丰富的资讯
and gives you rich information about what's in your images
而且今年我们还有一个新功能进一步推动图像理解
And this year we have a new feature that takes image understanding further
现在只要长按图片里的主体
Now when you touch and hold on the subject of an image
就能将其从背景提取出来
you can lift it away from the background and place it in apps like Messages
然后再拖放到信息 app 等各类 app 中
就像变魔术一样
It feels like magic
这实际上得益于一种先进的机器学习模型
It's actually the product of an advanced machine learning model
由 CoreML 和神经网络引擎加速
which is accelerated by CoreML
and the Neural Engine to perform 40 billion operations
在几毫秒之内执行 400 亿次运算
in just milliseconds
实况文本和 Visual Look Up 两大功能
Together, Live Text and Visual Look Up continue to unlock
源源不断地解锁照片和视频中丰富且有益的信息
rich and useful information from your photos and videos
覆盖了 iOS、iPadOS 和 macOS 各个系统
across iOS, iPadOS, and macOS
回到你了 Craig
Back to you, Craig
Craig: 这些智能功能可以帮助你轻松搞定各种事物
Craig: These intelligence features help you get things done with ease
另一个让生活更方便的 app
And another app that makes life easier is Wallet
是钱包 app
接下来有请 Corey 来给你介绍钱包 app 有些什么新东西
To tell you about what's new in Wallet, I'll hand it over to Corey
Corey Fugman: 凭借 Apple 钱包 app 我们正努力实现的终极目标
Corey Fugman: With Apple Wallet, we're working hard
就是取代你的实体钱包
on our goal to replace your physical wallet
比如将驾照和各类 ID 卡添加到钱包 app
Take what we're doing with driver's licenses and ID cards
很高兴我们已在马里兰和亚利桑那成功推出
We're excited to have launched Maryland and Arizona
在美国另外 11 个州也正积极展开部署
with 11 additional states actively working on deployments
最早接受钱包 app 中 ID 卡的是
And the first locations now accepting Wallet IDs
指定的 TSA 安全检查点
are select TSA security checkpoints
你也将能安全地向各类要求认证身份和年龄的 app 出示你的 ID
You'll also be able to securely present your ID
to apps requiring identity and age verification
基于隐私保护只有必须共享的信息才会被分享
To protect your privacy, only the necessary information will be shared
例如不需要提供你的详细生日日期
So rather than providing your exact birthday
只需分享你是 21 岁以上即可
you can simply share that you are over 21
现在让我们来聊聊各类钥匙
Now, let's talk about Keys
我们的钱包 app 里不断增加的各类钥匙
Our growing suite of keys in Wallet makes it easy to access everyday places
让你只需带着 iPhone 就可以轻松通行你的家、车、酒店和办公室
like your home, car, hotel, and office, all with just your iPhone
现在我们也让共享钥匙变得更简单
And now we're making sharing keys even easier
可通过你常用的几个通信 app
with your favorite messaging apps like Mail, Messages, or WhatsApp
如邮件 app、信息 app 或 WhatsApp 等
当你的朋友收到钥匙后
When your friend receives the key, they can add it to their Wallet
轻点一下就能将其加入自己的钱包 app
with a single tap
为了让你也能和没有 iPhone 的人分享
And to let you share keys with people who don't have an iPhone
我们也与 IETF 协作
we're working with the IETF to make sharing keys an industry standard
让共享钥匙成为一个行业标准让大家免费采用
that is free for others to adopt
我们的合作伙伴表现出极大的热情
We are seeing tremendous enthusiasm from our partners
纷纷表示希望加入以提供用于各类场所的钥匙
with more of them signing on to support keys for all of the places you visit
现在让我们来说说 Apple Pay 钱包 app 中最重要的一部分
Now let's talk about Apple Pay, one of the most important areas of Wallet
我们已经取得了很大进展
We've made a lot of progress with Apple Pay acceptance
各类商店和线上销售纷纷接受 Apple Pay
现在还正进一步扩展
in stores and online, and now we're expanding even further
这个月开始有了 iPhone 上的 Tap to Pay
Starting this month with Tap to Pay on iPhone
美国各地数百万商家可以直接通过 iPhone 接受非接触支付
millions of merchants across the U.S. can accept contactless payments
也不需要额外的硬件或支付终端
directly on iPhone with no additional hardware or payment terminal needed
借助支付提供商的 app
Beginning with apps from these payment providers
无论是小商户还是大零售商都能通过这个功能
Tap to Pay on iPhone enables small merchants and large retailers
用 iPhone 安全地接受付款
to use iPhone to securely accept payments
除了扩大接受范围
In addition to expanded acceptance, we're also enhancing Apple Pay
我们还提升了 Apple Pay
以支持新的支付类型
to support new types of payments
我们很高兴推出 Apple Pay Later
So we are thrilled to announce Apple Pay Later
该功能可让你将一笔 Apple Pay 支付款项
Apple Pay Later lets you split the cost of an Apple Pay purchase
分成四等额分摊在六周内还款
into four equal payments spread over six weeks
而且没有利息或任何费用
with zero interest and no fees of any kind
Apple Pay Later 在所有接受 Apple Pay 的地方均可使用
And Apple Pay Later is available everywhere Apple Pay is accepted
包括 app 内或者线上
in apps and online
例如你可以先买下心仪已久的这台咖啡机
You can now get that espresso machine you've wanted
之后再分期付款
and pay for it over time with no additional cost
而且无额外费用
开发者和商家们也不需担心
For developers and merchants, Apple Pay Later requires no integration
Apple Pay Later 不需要额外的整合开发
只需标准的 Apple Pay 即可
It just works using their standard Apple Pay implementation
分期还款通过钱包 app 管理
Upcoming payments are managed through Wallet
便于追踪什么时候该还什么款
making it easy to keep track of what's due when
帮你维持在预算范围内
and to stay within a budget
而且在你下单后
And after you've placed your order
我们还有一个全新功能帮助你追踪订单
we have another brand-new feature that helps you track it
Apple Pay Order Tracking 功能
Apple Pay Order Tracking enables merchants
使商家能将详细的收据和追踪信息
直接发送到钱包 app
to deliver detailed receipt and tracking information directly to Wallet
便于你获取 Apple Pay 订单的最新信息
making it easy to get the latest information
且这些信息都是安全私密地发送到你的设备
on all of your Apple Pay orders delivered securely and privately to your device
Apple Pay Order Tracking 功能将支持数以百万计的商家
Apple Pay Order Tracking will be offered at millions of merchants
基于 Shopify 等各大电商平台
through eCommerce platforms starting with Shopify
这就是我们给钱包 app 带来的更新
So that's our Wallet update. Back to you, Craig
交回给你 Craig
Craig: 有了更多地方接受钱包 app 里的 ID 卡
Craig: With ID cards available in more locations
以及使用和共享钥匙的新方式
new ways to use and share keys
还有Apple Pay Later 和 Apple Pay Order Tracking 等
Apple Pay Later, and Apple Pay Order Tracking
钱包 app 让我们生活更方便
Wallet makes life so much easier, no matter where you go
不管是去到何处
而带你到达目的地的好帮手
And the best way to get wherever you're going is with Maps
当然是地图 app
让我们出去看看地图 app 有些什么更新
So let's get out of here to talk about what's new
♪♪
我们不断完善地图 app
We're building the best map to help you navigate and explore the world
以助你导航和探索这世界
我们已经在 10 个国家和地区推出了新设计的地图
We've launched our redesigned map in ten countries and regions
很高兴宣布今年晚些时候
and we're excited to announce that later this year
将把新地图引入 11 个国家和地区
we'll bring the new map to 11 more, including France
包括法国、瑞士和新西兰
Switzerland, and New Zealand
我们的新地图有很多出色的功能
Our new map includes great features like cycling, Look Around, and so many more
包括骑行路线、四处看看等
通过新的城市体验
And with the new city experience, we pushed it even further
我们进一步增加了许多详尽新细节
例如土地覆盖、道路、高度信息等
with unprecedented detail for landcover, roads, and elevation
同时也优化了驾驶导航和公交信息
as well as improved driving and transit navigation
新增的城市如拉斯维加斯看起来美极了
And we're adding Las Vegas, which looks stunning
今年年底前我们将再添加 6 个城市
And before the end of the year, we'll add six more cities
包括迈阿密、芝加哥和悉尼
including Miami, Chicago, and Sydney
下面请 Meg 来介绍地图 app 的其他更新
To tell you more about what's new in Maps, here's Meg
Meg Frost: iOS 16 为地图 app 的用户和开发者带来了一系列出色的更新
Meg Frost: With iOS 16, we're introducing great updates
for Maps users and developers
首先让我们来看看呼声最高的功能之一
Let's start with one of our most requested features:
多途径点路线规划
multistop routing
你现在可以提前规划最多 15 个途径点
You can now plan up to 15 stops in advance
地图 app 现在会在“最近”保存途径的路线
Maps will now store previous routes in Recents so they're easy to get back to
便于你回看
你也可以事先在 Mac 上规划多途径点路线
and you can plan multi-stop routes on the Mac
出发前再发送到 iPhone
and send them to iPhone when you're ready to go
当然驾驶途中
And, of course, when you're driving
你也可以让 Siri 在路线添加新途径点
you can ask Siri to add additional stops to your route
不用分散注意力以确保行驶安全
while safely keeping your eyes on the road
接下来让我们来谈谈用公交出行
Next, let's talk about getting around with transit
乘客将能更方便地查看车费
We're making it easy for riders to see fares
来预估整个行程的费用
for how much their journey will cost
还能直接将交通卡添加到钱包 app 里
along with the ability to add transit cards to Wallet
交通卡余额不足时
And if a transit card balance is running low
你也会收到通知
, you'll receive an alert
让你无需离开地图 app 就可以充值
so you can reload it without having to leave Maps
我们也为开发者带来了 MapKit 的重大优化提升
And for developers, we're making big improvements to MapKit
首先是我们突破性的新城市体验
starting with our revolutionary new city experience
其中包括土地覆盖、道路、地标等丰富细节
which includes rich details for landcover, roads, landmarks, and more
比如 Bird app 这样的开发者现在就可以将这一详细的地图整合进自己的 app 中
Developers like Bird can now integrate this detailed map
便于用户寻找自行车和滑板车
so users can more easily locate bikes and scooters to get around town
在城里到处转转
而无论是在浅色模式还是深色模式下都看起来很美观
And it looks stunning in both Light and Dark Mode
还有更多
And there's more
我们也会将四处看看添加到 MapKit 里
We're also bringing Look Around to MapKit
这样就可以轻易将地图 app 的高清图像
making it easy to integrate high resolution imagery from Maps
引入到其他 app 如 Zillow
into apps like Zillow
帮助其用户在浏览房屋的时候获取沉浸式的视平线视图
helping users get an immersive ground-level view while browsing homes
最后我们也欣喜宣布今年晚些时候
And finally, we're excited to announce that later this year
开发者们将可以更快更灵活地
developers will have faster and more flexible ways
打造奇妙的地图体验
这都归功于全新的服务器端 API
to build incredible Maps experiences with brand-new server-side APIs
以上就是地图 app 更新的速览
And that's a quick look at Maps
交还给你 Craig！
Back to you, Craig!
Craig: 下面让我们来聊聊运动
Craig: Now, let's talk about sports
运动通过积极的方式让人们聚在一起
Sports can bring people together in meaningful ways
无论是朋友间的激烈竞争
whether a heated rivalry among friends
还是整个城市为当地队伍加油打气
or a whole town rooting for their team
在 Apple 我们希望能为世界各地的体育迷们打造精彩的体验
And at Apple, we want to create great experiences for sports fans everywhere
接下来有请 Rubie 为你介绍
To tell you more, here's Rubie
♪♪
Rubie Edmondson: 迄今为止有各种各样的方式让你随时关注自己喜爱的运动
Rubie Edmondson: Today, there are many ways to keep up with your favorite sports
例如向 Siri 询问运动员或者运动队的信息
like being able to ask Siri about players or teams
或是观看比赛实况
or see live games, no matter where they're streaming
无论是从哪里直播的
现在有了实时活动
And now with Live Activities, the Apple TV app brings you scores
Apple TV app 可以在你的锁屏上显示实时比分和解说
and play-by-play action right on your Lock Screen
我们最近还在 Apple TV+ 上首播 Friday Night Baseball
We also recently premiered Friday Night Baseball on Apple TV+
这样你可以每周五观看两场精彩赛事
where you can stream two great games every Friday
今天我们也为 Apple News 中的运动板块带来重大更新
And today, we have another major update for sports in Apple News
Apple News 在其提供服务的各个市场问鼎新闻类 app
Apple News is the number one news app everywhere it's available
现在将更让体育迷们有所期待
and it's about to become amazing for sports fans
你可以关注自己喜爱的运动队和比赛联盟
You can now follow your favorite teams and leagues to get stories
获取来自上百家优质媒体发布的新闻报道
这都将通过全新的 My Sports 板块
from hundreds of the best publishers in an all-new section called My Sports
你也可以查看顶级职业和大学体育联赛的比分、赛程、排名
You'll also find scores, schedules, and standings for the top professional
以及比赛亮点
and college sports leagues, and highlights too
还可以从新闻推送中直接获取你支持的队伍的精彩表现
Now you can catch the best plays from your favorite teams right in your news feed
你收藏的运动员或队伍有关内容也会直接同步到 Apple TV app
And your favorites are seamlessly synced with the Apple TV app
以及你所有的 Apple 设备
and across all your Apple devices
这一全新体育体验是免费的
This new sports experience is free
将在美国、英国、加拿大和澳大利亚推出
It'll be available in the U.S., UK, Canada, and Australia
如果你订阅了 Apple News+
And when you subscribe to Apple News+
还将获得许多来自当地报刊的优质体育报道
you'll get premium sports coverage from many local newspapers
以上就是有关运动的更新再回到你 Craig
That's Sports. Back to you, Craig
Craig: iOS 和整个 Apple 生态系统为全家带来了诸多精彩体验
Craig: iOS and the entire Apple ecosystem are amazing for families
我们今天将聊聊一些重要的新功能
and we have some great new features to talk about
先从家人共享的一些更新开始
starting with some updates to Family Sharing
通过家人共享你可以将喜爱的购买和订阅的服务
With Family Sharing, you can share your favorite purchases
共享给最多五位家庭成员
and subscriptions with up to five of your family members
包括 Apple Music iCloud+、Apple One 等等
including Apple Music, iCloud+, Apple One, and much more
这样家里每个人可以个性化定制自己喜爱的内容
Everyone gets personalized access to their favorite content
不需要再自己购买订阅
without having to buy their own subscriptions or share an account
或是和其他人共用一个账户
有孩子的家庭可以为小朋友创建专属的儿童账户
And for households with kids, you can create accounts just for them
内置了家长控制来帮你监督他们的屏幕使用时间
with built-in parental controls to help you monitor their screen time
或批准他们的购买
or approve their purchases
今年我们将进一步简化创建儿童账户的过程
And this year, we're making it even easier to create accounts for kids
以确保恰当的家长控制从一开始就实施起来
and make sure the right parental controls are in place right from the start
我们也将增加新方式便于设置年龄限制
We're adding a new, easy way to set age-appropriate restrictions
应用于各类 app、视频、书籍和音乐等
for apps, movies, books, and music
还有其他一些重要家长控制的快速设置
Along with quick setup of other important parental controls
给孩子设置新设备比如 iPad 将变得更加容易
We're also making setting up a new device for your child–
like an iPad–really simple
新设备开机后只需移近你的 iPhone
Just turn on the device they'll be using, bring your iPhone nearby
选择快速开始进行设置
and choose to set up with Quick Start
轻点几下小朋友的新设备就设置好可以用了
With just a few taps, the new device will be set up for their use
并且已经设好了你选择的家长控制
with all the parental controls you've selected already configured
当你的孩子要求更多屏幕使用时间的时候
And when your child asks for more screen time
你也不需要转到设置中去同意或不同意他们的要求
you won't have to navigate to Settings to approve or deny their request
直接在信息 app 回复就可以了
You can now respond right in Messages
最后我们还新增了家人共享核对清单
Finally, we've added a new Family Checklist with helpful tips
提供非常有帮助的提示
比如孩子长大了更新设置
like updating a child's settings as they get older
开启共享位置
turning on location sharing
或者就是提醒你可以与大家共享你的 iCloud+ 订阅
or just reminding you that you can share your iCloud+ subscription with everyone
这就是今年有关家人共享的一些功能更新
So those are some of the helpful updates to Family Sharing this year
我们知道大家都很喜欢与家人分享照片
Now, as we all know, one of the things
everyone enjoys sharing with their family is photos
所以今年我们优化了与家人共享照片的方式
So this year, we're introducing a better way to share photos with your family
我们珍贵的回忆一般可能是由不同的人拍下的
Our precious memories are often captured by several people
包括个人照片中的兴趣爱好、家庭项目和课业等
and in between personal photos of hobbies, house projects, and homework
还有我们的个人设备上那些家里人的照片全家人都想要
we have photos on our device that everyone in the family would like to have
但当然没有人会有所有的照片
But no one has all of them
所以家庭回忆永远没办法包含所有一切
so the family's memories are never complete
现在呢
Until now
我们带来了 iCloud 共享图库
We're introducing iCloud Shared Photo Library
帮助你顺利甚至自动与家人分享照片
to help you share photos seamlessly and even automatically
这很容易设置
It's easy to set up
它是一个单独的 iCloud 图库
It's a separate iCloud library that everyone can contribute to
家里每个人都可以上传、协作和浏览
collaborate on, and enjoy
你可以加入的共享图库
You can participate in one shared library
最多可以和 5 个人共享
that's shared with up to five other people
操作非常简单且只会共享你希望从自己图库中分享出去的照片
We've made it simple to share just the photos you want from your library
你可以分享图库里所有照片
You can share everything already in your library
或根据一个开始日期或照片里的人物进行筛选
or choose what to include based on a start date or the people in the photos
举例说你可以选择共享只有你与伴侣和孩子的照片
For example, you can choose to include just the photos
where you were together with your partner and the kids
共享图库设置好后
Once the Shared Library is set up
你也可以手动将刚拍下的照片转移过去
you can manually move over new photos after you take them
但我们还想更方便些
But we wanted to make it even easier with a new switch right in Camera
通过相机 app 里的一个新切换键
就可以在拍照的同时直接把照片发送到共享图库里
that sends shots straight to the Shared Library as you take them
这非常适用于度假旅行时可以即时共享照片
This is great when you're on a vacation and you want to make sure
the photos are shared right away
而当你在拍摄个人物品如一份礼物时
And if you take a photo of something personal, like a gift
也可随手关掉共享
you can easily turn it off
你甚至可以设置自动激活共享功能
You can also choose to have the sharing switch enabled automatically
这样你在共享图库的成员在附近拍照时就会启动
whenever you take shots with other members of the Shared Library nearby
这样如果你和家人去露营的话
So if you take photos on a camping trip, you don't have to remember
就不用担心忘记分享照片了
to share them later
在为你推荐标签页里会智能地提供共享建议
You'll also receive intelligent sharing suggestions in the For You tab
每人都有同样的权限
Everyone has equal permissions for adding, editing
在共享图库添加、编辑和删除照片
and deleting photos in the Shared Library
所以如果有家庭成员很会编辑照片
So if one member of the group is a talented photo editor
大家就可以欣赏编辑好的共享照片了
everyone gets to enjoy their edits to the shared photos
删除、标题和关键词也都是同步的
Deletions, captions, and keywords sync too
共享图库的内容会出现在所有人照片 app 的
Content in the Shared Library will appear in everyone's Memories
回忆、精选照片和小组件里
Featured Photos, and in the Photos widget
这样当你重温家庭之旅时所有的照片都会包含其中
So you can relive your family's adventures that include all the photos
这就是 iCloud 共享图库
That's iCloud Shared Photo Library:
与家人共享照片的最佳方法
the best way to share photos with your family
最后我们来聊聊隐私
And last, let's talk about privacy
我们一直致力于保护用户及其隐私
We're always working hard to protect our users and their privacy
提供了 App 隐私报告、邮件隐私保护
with features like App Privacy Report, Mail Privacy Protection
App 跟踪透明度、隐私标签等功能
App Tracking Transparency, Privacy Nutrition Labels
and so many more
另一个至关重要的点是保护用户的个人安全
Another critically important area is protecting our users' personal safety
我们正在开发一个新工具
One way we're doing that is by adding a new tool
帮助大家快速关闭其他人的访问权限
to help people quickly turn off others' access
比如有人想逃离一段虐待关系时可以停止位置共享
for example, disabling location sharing if they're escaping an abusive relationship
这就是安全检查功能
It's called Safety Check
下面请 Katie 来详细介绍
To tell you about it, here's Katie
Katie Skinner: 有很多人都和自己的伴侣共享他们设备的密码和访问权限
Katie Skinner: Many people share passwords
and access to their devices with their partner
然而若是处于虐待关系
However, in abusive relationships, this can threaten personal safety
这可能威胁到受害者个人安全
也阻碍他们求助
and make it harder for victims to get help
我们正和各类向家庭和亲密伴侣暴力的受害者提供帮助的组织密切合作
We've been working closely with organizations
that support victims of domestic and intimate partner violence
其中一项合作成果就是安全检查
And the result of those conversations is Safety Check
这是设置的新部分
a new section in Settings where you can quickly review and reset the access
让你可以快速查看和重置之前授予他人的访问权限
you've granted others
这样虐待关系受害者就可以快速撤销施暴人访问其数据和位置的权限
This lets people in abusive situations quickly revoke an abuser's access
to their data and location
以切断联系逃至安全之所
enabling them to cut ties and get to safety
安全检查可以阻止你的设备通过查找网络将位置共享给他人
Safety Check stops sharing your location with others via FindMy
并重置所有 app 的系统隐私权限
and resets the system privacy permissions for all apps
为了确保他人无法读取你的信息
It also protects access to your messages by helping you sign out of iCloud
它也能帮你退出所有其他设备上的 iCloud
on all your other devices
并将信息 app 和 FaceTime 通话的权限限制在手中的设备
and restricts Messages and FaceTime to the device in your hand
安全检查也能帮你来管理什么权限授予给什么人过
Safety Check also helps you manage who you've given access to
也能检查你给过哪些 app 什么样的权限
And you can audit which permissions you've granted to certain apps
我们的新举措得到了一些积极反馈
We've received some really positive feedback on our approach
包括美国 National Center for Victims of Crime
including from the National Center for Victims of Crime
也对此评论：
who said: "In times of crisis, for many survivors
“在危急时刻受害者如果知道谁掌握他们的信息和位置这无疑是至关重要的”
"it's important to know who has their information and location
“安全检查将控制权交还给受害者了“
Safety Check helps give control back to survivors."
这是很重要的工作
This is important work
让 iOS 进一步保护你的安全
expanding the ways iOS helps you stay safe
交回给你 Craig
Now, back to you, Craig
Craig: 保护你以及你的隐私
Craig: Protecting you and your privacy is and will always be
一直以来都是我们所做的核心
at the center of what we do
iOS 16 带来了那么多的更新将会改变你的 iPhone 体验
iOS 16 offers so many updates that will change the way you experience iPhone
iOS 还把这体验延伸到 iPhone 之外
iOS also extends that experience beyond the phone
提升你与周遭世界的互动体验
to enhance how you interact with the world around you
无论是优化你的晨间习惯
Whether helping you through your morning routine
还是在你下一个公路旅行帮你保持在线
or keeping you connected on your next road trip
都包在 iOS 身上
iOS has you covered
今年我们给你的家居和汽车体验带来了令人期待的功能更新
This year we're bringing exciting updates to your home and your car
有请 Corey 来给你谈谈家庭 app 的新功能
To tell you what's new in the home, here's Corey
♪♪
Corey Wang: 我们的家也许就是生活中最重要的地方
Corey Wang: Our home is perhaps the most important place in our lives
并且要管理的东西有很多
and there's a lot to manage
有了智能家居配件
Smart home accessories can make it easier
这就方便多了你可以直接通过 iPhone 管理你的家
and more convenient to control your home right from your iPhone
在办公桌边工作时查看谁在你家门口
You can do things like see who's at the door while working at your desk
或者不用下床就关掉楼下的灯
or turn off the lights downstairs without getting out of bed
不在家时
And when you're away from home
你也可以确认是否把前门上锁了
you can double-check if the front door is locked
或者提前调好温控
or adjust the temperature so it's just right when you get back
这样回到家时室内温度是刚好的
你的家还可以变得更智能
And your smart home is all the more powerful
尤其如果所有的配件能协同工作
when your accessories work together, reacting to changes automatically
自动应对各种变化
当然智能家居仍处于早期阶段
Now, the smart home is still in its early days
我们希望推动这些强大的功能
and we want to help bring these powerful experiences
带到尽可能多的家里
to as many homes as possible
要在家里建立一个连续互通的生态系统
In order to build a connected ecosystem at home
很重要的一点是你有各种选择
it's important that you have the most choice
而不必担心配件之间能否相互协作
so you don't have to worry about what works with what
考虑到这点
With that in mind, we joined forces with other industry leaders
我们和其他主流的业内伙伴一起
创立一个新的智能家居连接性标准
to create a new smart home connectivity standard
那就是 Matter
It's called Matter
Matter 让智能家居配件可以跨平台协同操作
Matter enables smart home accessories to work together across platforms
同时确保我们始终坚守的价值观
And to ensure we stayed true to our values
我们贡献了自己的智能家居体系 HomeKit
we contributed HomeKit, our smart home framework
作为新标准的基础
as a foundation of this new standard
这是为了确保 Matter 是建立在相同的核心原则上
so it's built on the same core principles
并保持最高级别的安全性
and maintains the highest level of security
业界的各大品牌都已陆续投入支持 Matter
Industry-leading brands have already committed to supporting Matter
有 130 多种产品正在生产计划中
with over 130 products in the pipeline, and that's just the beginning
而这只是开始
Matter 标准提供了连接智能家居配件的基石
The Matter standard provides the underlying foundation
也让我们得以在此基础上进行创新
to connect smart home accessories, and it allows us to innovate on top of it
我们进一步加强了隐私保护
We take privacy further
确保默认状态下你使用配件的数据都得以安全处理与储存
ensuring that data about how you use your accessories is processed
就连 Apple 本身也无法访问
and stored by default in a way that even Apple can't see
基于 Matter 我们将持续通过家庭 app 打造精彩的体验
With Matter, we can continue to create amazing experiences in the Home app
同时也确保所有各种配件
while also making sure all your different accessories
都同样便于设置和操作
are consistently simple to set up and easy to use
而现在你有更多的配件选项
And now that you’ll have more accessory options to choose from
让我们看看全新的家庭 app 如何让你的体验变得更棒
let's check out how we made the experience even better
with an all-new Home app
我们从底层架构开始进行了彻底的重新设计
We reimagined it from the ground up starting with the underlying architecture
让它更有效可靠
so it's more efficient and reliable
这对拥有许多配件的家来说尤其重要
especially for homes with many accessories
我们也彻底重新设计了你浏览、组织、查看各个配件的方式
We also completely redesigned how you navigate, organize
以更轻松地掌控你的智能家居
and view accessories to make it easier to control your smart home
我们将所有的房间和收藏项都整合进家庭 app 的首页
We've integrated your rooms and favorites into the main tab of the app
这样你可以一览无余整个家的情况
So you can see your entire home in a single view
使其看上去美观整洁
And we made sure it looks great, whether you're just getting started
不论你是智能家居的新手
还是搭建了整个先进且相互联通的家
or have built out an advanced connected home
我们还增加了温控、灯光、安全等新类别
We added new categories for climate, lights, security, and more
并在屏幕顶部添加了每个类别情况的概览
and an overview of what's happening in each category
right at the top of the screen
通过类别还可以轻松浏览家庭 app
And categories are a great way to navigate within the app
当你轻点一个特定类别
When you tap on a specific category, you see all the relevant accessories
就可以按房间查看所有有关配件
以及更详细的状态信息
organized by room and more detailed status information
中心位置则是多摄像头视图可一次查看四个
A multi-camera view displays up to four cameras at once front and center
右扫既能查看其他额外的摄像头
and you can scroll to the right to see any additional cameras
我们也重新设计了每个模块
We also redesigned tiles so that different accessories
让你能通过形状和颜色轻易识别不同的配件
are more visually recognizable through shape and color
现在有了新的锁定屏幕上的小组件
And with the new widgets on the Lock Screen, it's easier than ever
要查看你的智能家居情况也就更方便了
to see how your home is doing
这就是全新的家庭 app
So that's the all-new Home app, and it's coming to iPhone, iPad, and Mac
很快也将在 iPhone、 iPad 和 Mac 推出
现在你有了掌控家居的工具
Now that you have what you need to keep tabs on your home
可以准备上车出发了
you're ready to hit the road
让我们交给 Emily 来给你介绍 CarPlay 车载
Let's hand it off to Emily to talk about CarPlay
Emily Schubert: CarPlay 车载让你在车上可以更智能和安全地使用 iPhone
Emily Schubert: CarPlay is the smarter, safer way to use your iPhone in the car
也从根本上改变了人们和汽车的交互方式
and has fundamentally changed the way people interact with their vehicles
几乎全美 98% 的汽车都可以使用
It's available on over 98% of cars in the U.S
更重要的是有 79% 的美国买家表示
What's more, 79% of U.S. buyers
只会考虑购买配有 CarPlay 车载的汽车
would only consider a car that works with CarPlay
这是买新车时必有的功能
It's a must-have feature when shopping for a new vehicle
我们的用户非常喜爱 CarPlay 车载
Our users love CarPlay
它让用户可以非常便捷地在车中使用各类 app 同时采用他们所熟悉的 iPhone 交互界面
It gives them an easy way to use apps in the car
using the familiar UI from their iPhone
但汽车也经历了很大的变化
But cars have changed a lot
比如屏幕尺寸变大了
with larger-sized screens and more of them throughout the car
也有更多屏幕分布全车
iPhone 也因此有机会扮演更重要的角色
There's an opportunity for iPhone to play an even more important role
我们正与汽车制造商们合作
We've been working with automakers to reinvent the in-car experience
携手重塑各类车内屏幕的体验
across all of the driver's screens
让我们来看看新一代的 CarPlay 车载
Let's take a sneak peek at this next generation of CarPlay
♪♪
有好多值得探索的
There's so much to explore here
让我们仔细看看
Let's take a closer look
新一代的 CarPlay 车载将在各个驾驶屏幕上提供内容
This next generation of CarPlay provides content for all the driver's screens
让你拥有统一且一致的体验
giving an experience that is unified and consistent
结合了你的车和 iPhone 的优势
It's the very best of both your car and your iPhone
它也带来了比现有 CarPlay 车载更多的功能
And it goes beyond what you can do with CarPlay today
与车辆硬件系统的深度整合
Deep integration with the car's hardware lets you tune your car's radio
让你无需退出 CarPlay 车载就可以直接操控车子的收音机或空调
or change your temperature without ever leaving the CarPlay experience
它还包括由你 iPhone 支持的小组件
It also includes widgets, powered by your iPhone
都可匹配呈现于屏幕上
that fit your screens perfectly
这些小组件也将出现在你的仪表盘中心
They can live front and center in the gauge cluster as well
让你一目了然各种信息
giving you information at a glance
而且新一代的 CarPlay 车载将与你整个仪表盘相互沟通
In fact, this next generation of CarPlay powers your entire instrument cluster
为此
To do this, your iPhone communicates
你的 iPhone 会以设备端且保护隐私的方式与车辆的实时系统连接
in an on-device, privacy-friendly way
with your vehicle's real-time systems
呈现你各种的驾驶信息
showing all of your driving information like speed, RPMs
如车速、RPM、油位、温度等
fuel level, temperature, and more
而且无论你的车有多么独特的屏幕形状或布局
And no matter what type of unique screen shapes or layouts you may have
新一代的 CarPlay 车载
this next generation of CarPlay feels like
都会像是专为你的车子设计的一样
it was made specifically for your car
我们也很高兴你可以打造出专属于自己的驾驶核心体验
We're also excited to give you the ability
to make the core of the driving experience unique to you
我们精心设计了一系列仪表盘选项
We carefully crafted instrument cluster options
包含了现代和传统风格
ranging from the modern to the traditional
还可以选择不同的颜色
that use different colors
仪表盘风格、背景和布局
dial treatments, backgrounds, and layouts
呈现出独特的外表和感觉
to provide various looks and feels
你可以为你的仪表盘选择各式各样的精选主题和风格
You can choose different curated themes and styles for your gauges
遍布全球的汽车制造商们也很期待
And automakers from around the world are excited
能为用户们带来全新的 CarPlay 车载
to bring this new vision of CarPlay to customers
这只是新一代 CarPlay 车载更新的初步介绍
This is just a taste of what the next generation of CarPlay will bring
明年晚些时候发布的汽车将陆续搭载
Vehicles will start to be announced late next year
我们也迫不及待在今后为你带来更多
and we can't wait to show you more further down the road
好了现在再把镜头还给 Craig
And now, I'll hand it back to Craig
Craig: 这就是 iOS 16
Craig: And that's iOS 16
这一重大版本更新让你用新颖的方式来打造属于自己的 iOS
a mighty release that gives you entirely new ways to make iOS your own
帮你轻松保持联系
It also helps you stay in touch with ease, engage with the world around you
与周遭世界互动
和亲朋好友共享体验和回忆
and seamlessly share experiences and memories with your family and friends
而这只是开头
And that's just the beginning
我们也为 AirPods 的空间音频进行了优化提升
We've also made a big advancement in Spatial Audio with AirPods
空间音频功能基于对声音与我们头型和耳型如何交互的理解
Now, Spatial Audio works by understanding how sound interacts
with the geometry of your head and ears
现在 iOS 16 中你可以利用手机的原深感摄像头
And now, in iOS 16, you can use the True Depth camera on iPhone
创建个性化的空间音频档案
to create a personalized Spatial Audio profile
从而实现更准确而沉浸式的听觉体验
enabling an even more precise
且专门为你量身定制
and immersive listening experience, tuned just for you
此外快速备忘录也将来到 iOS
Plus, Quick Note is coming to iOS so you can capture ideas instantly
便于你即时记录灵感
新的快速安全响应机制
A new rapid security response mechanism
让 iPhone 能更快进行安全优化
gets important improvements to iPhone faster
此外你还将有更多拟我表情的选项
and you've got more Memoji customizations to choose from
还有更多新功能随时随地满足你所需
And there's so many more features to meet your needs no matter where you are
接下来我把时间交给 Kevin
Now, I’ll hand it over to Kevin
来介绍 Apple Watch 的重大更新
to tell you about the big new advancements coming to Apple Watch
♪♪
Kevin Lynch: 让我们来聊聊 watchOS
Kevin Lynch: Let's talk about watchOS
Apple Watch 一直以来都是全球最受欢迎的手表
Apple Watch continues to be the most loved watch in the world
能帮你保持紧密联系、时刻活力满满乐享健康生活
because it helps you stay connected, active, and healthy
watchOS 9 也将在这三方面带来一系列出色的新功能
In watchOS 9 we're bringing great new features to each of these three areas
首先你可以密切留意关注的事
First, you can stay connected to what matters to you most
只需看一眼你的手腕间
just by glancing at your wrist
不管你用的是广受欢迎的照片表盘
whether you use the popular Photos watch face
还是有丰富复杂功能的表盘
or a face with rich complications
我们也添加了四个新的表盘供你选择
And we're adding four new watch faces for you to choose from
天文表盘经过重新设计
The Astronomy face has been remastered to take advantage of the expansive display
可以充分利用更大的显示屏
展示世界各地实时的云层覆盖
and shows current cloud coverage around the world
月相表盘可用来了解
The Lunar calendar is used to observe traditional holidays
许多文化中的传统节日和特别活动
and special events in many cultures
这个表盘也是对延续了千年传统习俗的一种赞颂
The Lunar watch face celebrates this thousand-year-old practice
支持农历、伊斯兰历和希伯来历
with support for Chinese, Islamic, and Hebrew calendars
还有艺术家 Joi Fulton 设计的欢乐时光表盘
Play Time, designed by artist Joi Fulton
其特色是异想天开的数字动画显示时间
features whimsical animated numbers
你可以轻点显示屏让它们跳动
You can tap the display to send them bouncing around
在你放下手腕后它们也就会休息一下
and when you lower your wrist, they take a nap
最后大都会表盘以新字型突显手表的风格
Finally, Metropolitan highlights watch typography with a new font
当你旋转数码表冠时字型也会随着动态拉伸
that dynamically stretches when you rotate the digital crown
这表盘还提供了缤纷的颜色组合
and features many lovely color combinations
丰富的复杂功能让你能在小空间内查看更多信息
Rich complications enable you to see more information in a small space
而我们将这些功能带到更多表盘上
and we're bringing these to more of our watch faces
watchOS 9 也推出了全新的 Siri UI 和新的横幅通知
watchOS 9 also introduces a refreshed Siri UI and new banner notifications
开启着的 app 也将置于程序坞便于你快速访问
And active apps will be pinned to the top of the Dock for quick access
另一个保持联系的方式就是收听最新的故事
Another way to stay connected is by listening to the latest stories
或者分享你喜欢的内容
or sharing your favorite content
watchOS 9 的播客 app
With watchOS 9, the Podcast app allows you to discover
让你通过搜索和现在就听功能来探索并关注新播客内容
and follow new podcasts using Search and Listen Now
现在孩子们也可以通过家人共享设置使用播客 app
And the app is now available to kids using Family Setup
对于开发者们来说
For developers, sharing content and selected images from apps like Outcast
从 Outcast 或者微信等 app 分享内容和共享已选择图片将更容易
这得益于新的共享表单和照片选择器 API
and WeChat is easier with the new Share Sheet and Photos Picker APIs
凭借 CallKit
And with CallKit, you can start, end, or mute VoIP calls from apps
你可以直接在 Apple Watch 上
拨打、挂断或静音来自 Webex 此类 app 的 VoIP 通话
like Webex directly on Apple Watch
这就是 watchOS 9 将带来的新功能让你保持联系
That's some of what's coming in watchOS 9 to keep you connected
接下来让 Craig 来聊聊助你活力满满的各项更新
And now to Craig to tell you what's coming to keep you active
Craig Bolton: 体能训练 app 是最受欢迎的 app 之一
Craig Bolton: The Workout app is one of the most popular apps
所以这次的 watchOS 9
so in watchOS 9, we're bringing new easy-to-use metrics
推出了一系列全新且易用的指标、视图和训练体验
得益于顶级的运动员们提供的灵感启发
views, and training experiences inspired by high-performing athletes
先从跑步说起
starting with running
这项运动不管你的水平如何
It's a sport that, no matter what your level
都可以使用指标更好了解你的表现
you can use metrics to better understand your performance
相应地调整训练也能减少受伤机率
And switching up your training can reduce the chance of getting injured
我们首先添加了三项新的跑姿测量指标
The first thing we're doing is adding three new running form metrics
以追踪你跑步的效率
to track how efficiently you run
但要从手腕测量这些并不简单
Measuring these from the wrist isn't easy
比如垂直振幅
Take vertical oscillation for example
是衡量你上下移动幅度的指标
which is a measure of how much you move up and down
如果幅度过高
If it's too high, your energy might be wasted going up
代表你消耗太多能量往上移而不是往前推进
versus propelling you forward
要从手腕测量这个
In order to capture this from the wrist
我们必须从你手臂摆动的独特性推测你的躯干运动
we need to extrapolate your torso movement
from the distinctive style of your arm swing
我们使用了机器学习和传感器融合
We use machine learning and sensor fusion–
也就是加速感应器和陀螺仪的组合
a combination of accelerometer and gyroscope–
将躯干运动分离出来
to isolate your torso movement
再测量其产生的垂直振幅
and then measure how much vertical oscillation is produced
我们也用类似方法来测量另外两个跑姿测量指标
We use a similar approach to measure the two other Running Form metrics–
步长和触地时间
stride length and ground contact time
这些指标可以被添加到全新且易于查看的体能训练视图
These metrics can be added to new easy-to-read Workout views
每个视图都有更多指标让你一目了然
Each Workout view lets you see more at a glance
滚动数码表冠就可查看常见指标的新视图
Scroll the digital crown to see new views
for familiar metrics like segments
如分段、单段和爬升高度
splits, and elevation
新推出的还有心率区间
And we're introducing heart rate zones
便于你快速查看自己所处的区间
so you can quickly see what zone you're in
随时了解自己的训练强度
and get a sense of your intensity level at any point during your workout
同时还有新的自定义训练计划
There's also a new custom workout
让你规划自己的跑步训练
that you can use to add structure into your run
举个例子如果你是想提高速度或耐力
For example, if you are trying to improve your speed or endurance
就可以基于距离和时间段来创建一套训练与恢复计划
you can create a workout using distance and time intervals
让你可以重复进行
that include sets of work and recovery which you can repeat as needed
你还可以在训练的指定部分添加一些新提示
You can also add one of the new alerts to a specific part of your workout–
比如专门用来提醒你的心率区间目标
like one to monitor which heart rate zone you want to train in
帮助你保持在训练目标上
to help keep you on track
当你跑步时这些提示可以通过触觉和声音反馈指引你
During your run, these alerts will guide you
with both haptics and voice feedback
让你知道何时在训练和恢复间进行切换
letting you know when to switch between work and recovery
或者提醒你加速如果你的心率低于目标区间时
and when to pick up the pace if your heart rate falls below
the target zone that you set
跑步时你也可以使用数码表冠
During your run, you can use the Digital Crown
查看其他的训练视图
for additional workout views like this new power metric
比如这个新的功率指标
设定功率目标的话
Running with a power target can help you go the distance
可以帮助确保能量消耗在可持续的范围内让你跑得更远
by keeping your effort in a range that you can reasonably sustain
你甚至还可以查看你的体能训练对健身记录圆环的贡献
You can even see how this workout is contributing to your Activity rings
而且如果你经常使用一个跑步路线
And if it's a route you do often, it will be automatically saved
你的体能训练 app 会将其自动保存起来
让你可以和自己上次或最佳时间进行赛跑
in the Workout app for you to race against your last or best time
来了解自己坚持锻炼的成效如何
That way, you can see if all the training you're doing is paying off
这么多新的功能也不仅用于跑步
You can use many of these new features not just when you're running
也可用于其他类型
but for many workout types like Hiking
如徒步、高强度间歇训练和功能性力量训练
HIIT, and Functional Strength Training
铁人三项运动员可以使用新的多项目运动
And for our triathletes, there's a new multi-sport workout type
利用传感器融合来检测你何时完成了某个单项
that uses sensor fusion to detect when you finish one leg of your race
并过渡到下一项
and are transitioning to the next
所以就实现自动切换从游泳到单车再到跑步
So it can automatically switch between swimming, cycling, and running
这就是 watchOS 9 的体能训练 app 将带来的部分新功能
That's just some of what's coming to the Workout app in watchOS 9
从初代 Apple Watch 推出以来我们一直收到用户们的故事而深受鼓舞
Since the first Apple Watch, we've been inspired by the stories
他们每天充满动力努力合上健身记录圆环
we hear from users who stay motivated by closing their Activity rings each day
我们也知道有很多 iPhone 用户也想达成他们的锻炼目标
We also know there are many iPhone users who want to meet
但没有 Apple Watch
their fitness goals but don't yet have an Apple Watch
所以在 iOS 16 所有 iPhone 用户将可以使用体能训练 app
So in iOS 16, the Fitness app will be available to all iPhone users
利用 iPhone 的各个运动感应器
Using the iPhone motion sensors
你可以通过常用的 app 追踪步数、行走距离、爬升高度和体能训练
you can track steps, distance
flights climbed, and workouts from your favorite apps
将其转换成动态卡路里的估值
which can be converted to an estimation of your active calories
从而贡献到你每日的活动目标
to contribute to your daily Move goal
你也可以把活动圆环共享给朋友
You'll also be able to share your Move ring with friends
询问技巧指导和建议
and receive coaching tips
Apple Watch 给你提供全天候的健身记录
While Apple Watch gives you a picture of your all-day activity
我们很高兴能将体能训练 app 的一些好处带给 iPhone 用户
we're excited to bring some of the Fitness app benefits to iPhone users
让他们也开始健身
to get them started on their fitness journey
现在让 Sumbul 来介绍 watchOS 9 帮你乐享健康生活的新功能
Now, I'll hand it off to Sumbul to tell you what's coming in watchOS 9
to help keep you healthy
♪♪
Sumbul Ahmad Desai: 很多人都因为睡眠 app 获益良多
Sumbul Ahmad Desai: The Sleep app has helped millions of you
它可以助你了解自己的睡眠质量
by providing insights into how much sleep you're getting
以及睡眠时的心率、呼吸频率和血氧等指标
along with metrics like heart rate
respiratory rate, and blood oxygen
watchOS 9 的睡眠阶段功能能让你更了解自己的睡眠
In watchOS 9, you'll be able to learn more about your sleep with Sleep Stages
Apple Watch 通过加速感应器和心率传感器的信号
Apple Watch uses signals from the accelerometer and heart rate sensor
来检测你所处的睡眠阶段
to detect which stage of sleep you're in
机器学习模型根据多导睡眠图的临床黄金标准经过训练和验证
Machine learning models were trained and validated
against the clinical gold standard of polysomnography with the largest
参考了可穿戴设备有史以来最大和最多样化人群的研究
and most diverse population ever studied for a wearable
你可以查看在每个阶段睡了多久
You can see how much time you spent in each stage
以及大概什么时候睡醒的
as well as when you might have woken up
在健康 app 还有更多详细信息
You'll see more details in the Health app where you'll learn
让你了解每个睡眠阶段从快速眼动期、核心睡眠到深度睡眠阶段
that each sleep stage– REM, Core, and Deep–
所扮演的重要角色
perform an essential function
且你睡觉时很可能会在这些睡眠阶段反复循环
And as you sleep, you're likely to cycle through these stages multiple times
学者们还在研究睡眠时所发生的事情
Researchers are still looking into what happens during sleep
及其它对健康的影响
and how it impacts your health
我们希望能帮助推动睡眠科学
We want to help push forward the science of sleep
因此 Apple Heart and Movement Study 的参与者
so Apple Heart and Movement Study participants will now be able
将可透过 Research app 贡献睡眠阶段数据
to contribute sleep stage data through the Research app
鉴于此研究规模之大
With the large scale of this study, we are excited about the potential discoveries
我们很期待这可能带来的新发现
这就是睡眠 app 的更新
That's what's new with sleep
另一个 Apple Watch 起到重要影响的是心脏健康
Another area where Apple Watch has an impact is heart health
我们得知有许多用户因收到房颤提示
We hear from so many of you who have received an Atrial Fibrillation alert
而寻求到性命攸关的及时护理
and sought potentially-life saving care
所以我们也希望能为接受诊断的你提供支持
So we also wanted to offer support once you've been diagnosed
对于有房颤历史的人来说
When living with this condition, it's important to understand
了解自己的房颤时长是非常重要的
the time you spend in AFib because it may relate
因为这可能涉及患有严重并发症如中风的风险
to your risk of serious complications, such as stroke
watchOS 9 可通过房颤历史来追踪你的房颤时长
watchOS 9 can now track the amount of time
your heart shows signs of this rhythm with AFib History
而在健康 app
And in the Health app, you can manage lifestyle factors
你也可以管理数个可能影响你房颤时长的生活因素
that may influence the amount of time you spend in AFib
如运动、睡眠和体重
like exercise, sleep, and weight
房颤历史甚至帮你辨别一天或一周内
AFib History even helps you identify the time of the day or week
你房颤最频繁的时刻
when your AFib is most frequent
你也可以生成 PDF 共享给自己的医生
You can also share a PDF with your doctor to facilitate richer conversations
有助于更有意义的讨论
房颤历史是首个长期特别提供房颤信息的功能
AFib History is a first-of-its-kind feature
that uniquely provides insights into your AFib over the long term
我们预计将很快获得 FDA 的许可
We expect to receive FDA clearance for AFib History soon
Apple Watch 使得你的健康管理中那些较为复杂的方面
Apple Watch makes some of the more complicated aspects
变得更为直观易懂
of your health more intuitive
今年我们还着手处理对大家健康同样不可或缺的另一方面
And this year, we're tackling another integral aspect of health
用药
for so many of us–Medications
超过 50% 的人群在服用各类处方药
Over 50% of people take prescription medications
我们希望能帮助你
and we wanted to help make it easier to track, manage
更轻松地追踪、管理和了解你的用药
and understand the medications that you take
所以 watchOS 9 里的用药 app 将帮你
So in watchOS 9, the Medications app makes it easy for you to discreetly
审慎且方便地随时追踪药物、维生素和营养品
and conveniently track your medications
vitamins, and supplements anytime
你可以记录偶尔的用药
You can log medications that you might take occasionally
比如抗过敏的西替利嗪
like Cetirizine for allergies
也可以收到通知提醒你定期用药
And you can receive notifications for medications
that you need to take regularly
表盘上丰富的复杂功能也能帮你时刻掌握用药时间
Rich complications on your watch face can help you stay on top of your schedule
当然你也能从健康 app 追踪与管理用药
And of course you can track and manage your medications in the Health app
就算你没有 Apple Watch 也可以
even if you don't have an Apple Watch
要创建你的用药清单
To build your medications list
只需将输入药名就会出现用药建议
start typing the name, and you'll see suggestions
我们希望能简化这个过程
We wanted to make creating the list easier
尤其如果你服用多种药物
especially if you take multiple medications
所以你只需使用 iPhone 相机扫描药物标签即可
So you can just use your iPhone camera to scan the label of your medication
你也可以制定时间表来接收提醒
You can create a schedule to receive reminders
还能添加自定义视觉效果帮你记得用药
and add custom visuals to make it easier to remember
用药的另一个重要方面是药物间的相互作用
Another important aspect of medications is drug-drug interactions
有时可能降低效果或者引起副作用
which can make them less effective or cause side effects
单在美国每年因药物相互作用而入院的人高达 25 万
In the U.S. alone, drug interactions cause nearly
a quarter of a million hospitalizations each year
为了帮你解决此问题
To help you with this, you'll receive an alert when you add a new medication
每当你添加用药时如果会有危急的相互作用就会出现提示
if there is a critical interaction
我们与顶级的医学出版社 Elsevier 合作
We've partnered with Elsevier, a leading medical publisher
在用药 app 的各个环节提供临床准确且基于证据的信息
to provide clinically accurate and evidence-based information
across the Medications experience
这样你就能够查看危急、严重或一般的相互作用
You'll be able to review critical, serious, and moderate interactions
以及与酒精等的相互作用
as well as interaction factors like alcohol
用药 app 也适用于健康共享
Medications also works with Health Sharing
这也是 iOS 16 的更新之一
which is updated in iOS 16
你现在可以向家庭成员发送邀请
You can now send a family member an invitation
让他们共享健康数据
to share their health data with you
这样你不仅可以在亲人的健康之旅提供支持
This is another way that you can support a loved one on their health journey
也可以获得安心
and have peace of mind, too
现在回到 Kevin
Now back to Kevin
你的健康数据是你最私密的信息之一
Kevin: Your health data is some of your most personal information
而隐私保护是我们打造 Apple Watch 和设计各项功能的核心
and privacy is central to how we build and design features for Apple Watch
你的健康数据都在设备端加密
Health data is encrypted on device
未经你的明确许可无法共享
and is not shared without your explicit permission
你还会定期收到提醒你正在共享哪些健康数据
You'll also now be periodically reminded of what health data you're sharing
以及与谁共享
and who you're sharing it with
watchOS 9 中还有很多其他功能
There's so much more in watchOS 9
包括对 6 种新键盘语言的支持
including support for six new keyboard languages
以及让开发者可以将 watchOS 上的 app 与 Apple TV 连接起来的新方式
a new way for developers to connect their watchOS apps to Apple TV
此外通过家人共享设置孩子们可以直接从他们的手腕上
and with Family Setup, kids can now control home devices
控制家庭 app 里的设备
right from their wrist
watchOS 是最先进的可穿戴操作系统
watchOS is the world's most advanced wearable operating system
watchOS 9 通过各项全新功能
and watchOS 9 takes it further
更进一步地让你保持紧密联系
with new features to help you stay connected
时刻活力满满乐享健康生活
active, and healthy
接下来交给 Craig
Back to Craig
watchOS 9 真让人兴奋
Craig: I'm so excited for watchOS 9
我很期待将它交到用户们的手中
and can't wait to get it into the hands of our users
接下来 John 会向大家展示 Mac 的新功能
Next, to show you what's new with Mac, here's John
♪♪
我们很高兴看到
John Ternus: We couldn't be more excited
Mac 向 Apple 芯片的过渡进展顺利
by how well the Mac transition to Apple Silicon is going
整个过渡计划从 M1 芯片的发布开始 M1 芯片为 Mac 带来了突破性的性能
It all started with the launch of M1, which brought a whole new level
功能和电池续航
of performance, capabilities, and battery life to the Mac
我们几乎已经完成了整个 Mac 产品线的过渡
We've already transitioned nearly the entire Mac product line
这些搭载 M1 系列芯片的新系统带来了强大的功能
Users have been blown away by the phenomenal capabilities
让用户们大为惊喜
of these new systems powered by the M1 family of chips
整个 Mac 产品业务蒸蒸日上
And the Mac business has never been stronger
今天我们非常高兴为 Mac 开启
Well, today we're excited to start the next generation
下一代的 Apple 芯片
of Apple Silicon for the Mac
这就是
Introducing..
M2 芯片
M2
它进一步提升了 M1 芯片的突破性性能和功能
It takes the breakthrough performance and capabilities of M1 even further
接下来就请 Johny 来为你详细讲解
To tell you more, I'll pass it over to Johny
今天我们推出了专为 Mac 设计的
Johny Srouji: Today we begin our second generation of Apple Silicon
第二代 Apple 芯片
designed specifically for the Mac
M 系列芯片驱动了各种强大的性能和功能
The M-Series chips deliver a scalable range of performance and capabilities
从 M1 芯片开始带来了一系列突破性功能
It began with M1's breakthrough set of features
为我们广受欢迎的产品带来了重大转变
that transformed our most popular systems
M2 芯片是 M 系列芯片的第二代
M2 starts the second generation of M-Series chips
它进一步地提升了 M1 芯片的功能
and goes beyond the remarkable features of M1
和业内那些通过提高芯片功率而提升性能的方法相比
Unlike others in the industry who significantly increase power
我们采取了不同的做法
to gain performance, our approach is different
我们持续不懈地关注高能效表现
We continue to have a relentless focus on power efficient performance
换句话说我们在使性能最大化的同时最大限度地降低功耗
In other words, maximizing performance while minimizing power consumption
结合我们的统一内存架构和定制技术
Combined with our unified memory architecture and custom technologies
这种对能效的关注让 M2 芯片可以将更高的性能和更多新功能
this focus on power efficiency allows M2 to bring even more performance
带给我们最受欢迎的 Mac 产品
and new capabilities to our most popular Macs
M2 芯片采用增强的
M2 is built using an enhanced
第二代 5 纳米制程技术
second-generation five nanometer technology
并封装了超过 200 亿个晶体管
and features over 20 billion transistors:
比 M1 芯片多了 25%
that's 25% more than M1
我们用这些晶体管来增强芯片的每一个功能
We use those transistors to enhance every feature of the chip
首先是内存控制器
starting with the memory controller
它能提供 100GB/s 的统一内存带宽
which delivers 100GB/s of unified memory bandwidth
这比 M1 芯片多了 50% 也带来了更高的性能
which is 50% more than M1 for even greater performance
并且由于 M1 芯片功能强大用户可以运行各种对性能有高要求的任务
And because M1 is so capable, users run all sorts of demanding tasks
所以在 M2 上我们启用了高达 24GB 的统一内存
So for M2, we've enabled up to 24GB of unified memory
来处理更巨大也更复杂的工作负载
to handle even larger and more complex workloads
M2 芯片采用了我们新一代的中央处理器
M2 features our next-generation CPU
在性能核心和能效核心方面都取得了进步
with advancements in both the performance and efficiency cores
性能核心速度更快具备更大的缓存
The performance cores are faster and feature a larger cache
而能效核心得到了显著增强
and the efficiency cores have been significantly enhanced
能带来更大的性能提升
for even greater performance gains
它们协同配合用非常少的功耗就能轻松完成需要重度使用中央处理器的任务
Together, they rip through CPU-intensive tasks using very little power
如果我们把 M2 芯片的多核中央处理器性能与 M1 芯片相比较
When we look at the multi-core CPU performance of M2 compared to M1
就能发现它的性能提升了 18%
it delivers 18% greater performance
而与最新的 10 核 PC 笔记本电脑芯片相比
And compared to the latest 10-core PC laptop chip
M2 芯片的中央处理器在相同功耗下
the CPU in M2 delivers nearly two times faster performance
能带来将近两倍的性能
at the same power level
M2 芯片仅使用了 PC 芯片四分之一的功耗
And M2 delivers the peak performance of the PC chip
就能提供 PC 芯片的峰值性能
while using a quarter of the power
如果把 M2 芯片与最新的 12 核 PC 笔记本电脑芯片相比
Now let's compare M2 to the latest 12-core PC laptop chip
就会发现 12 核的 PC 笔记本电脑芯片
which needs dramatically more power
需要大幅增加功耗才能提高性能
to deliver an increase in performance
所以搭载 12 核 PC 笔记本电脑芯片的系统会变得更厚、更烫、更吵
So it's in a thicker, hotter, more noisy system
电池续航时间也更短
with less battery life
M2 芯片能提供 12 核芯片接近 90% 的峰值性能
M2 delivers nearly 90% of the peak performance of the 12-core chip
而功耗仅需其四分之一
while using just a quarter of the power
这就是我们所说的 Apple 芯片的
This is what we mean by the power efficient performance
能效表现
of Apple Silicon
M2 芯片还配备了我们新一代的图形处理器
M2 also features our next generation GPU
拥有多达 10 个核心比 M1 芯片多两个
which now has up to 10 cores– that's two more than M1
10 核图形处理器集成了更大的缓存和更高的内存带宽
Combined with a larger cache and higher memory bandwidth
能够极大提升图形性能
the 10-core GPU delivers a big boost in graphics performance
在与 M1 芯片相同的功耗水平下
M2 delivers up to 25% higher graphics performance
M2 芯片的图形性能提升最高可达 25%
at the same power level as M1
并且在其最大功耗水平下性能提升最高可达 35%
and up to 35% higher performance at its max
与最新的 PC 笔记本电脑芯片中的集成显卡性能相比
And compared to the integrated graphics in the latest PC laptop chip
M2 芯片的图形处理器能在相同功耗下具有最快可达 2.3 倍的性能
the GPU in M2 delivers 2.3 times faster performance at the same power level
M2 芯片只需要五分之一的功耗
And M2 delivers the peak performance of the PC chip
就能实现 PC 芯片的峰值性能
using just one-fifth of the power
M2 芯片具有卓越的性能功耗比
This much higher performance per watt from M2
它让系统冷静运行 并带来超长电池续航
enables systems to run cool and quiet with exceptional battery life
而且打造自有芯片的优势之一
Now, one of the advantages of making our own silicon
就是我们很快就能把最新的定制技术
is that we can quickly bring our newest custom technologies
引入我们所有的 SoC 芯片
across our SoCs
所以 M2 芯片还搭载了我们最新一代的安全隔区和神经网络引擎
So M2 also features our next-generation Secure Enclave and Neural Engine
M2 芯片中的神经网络引擎每秒可以处理 15.8 万亿次操作
The Neural Engine in M2 can process up to 15.8 trillion operations per second
这比 M1 芯片快了 40%
That's over 40% more than M1
它也配备了我们的新一代的媒体处理引擎
It also has our next generation media engine
包括支持 8K H.264 和 HEVC 视频的
including a higher-bandwidth video decoder
更高带宽视频解码器
that supports 8K H.264 and HEVC video
而且 M2 芯片还配备了强大的 ProRes 视频处理引擎
And M2 features our powerful ProRes video engine
用于硬件加速编解码
for hardware accelerated encode and decode
所以搭载 M2 芯片的系统能够播放多条 4K 和 8K 的视频
So systems with M2 will be able to play back multiple streams of 4K and 8K video
这就是 M2 芯片
So that's M2
它开启了新一代的 M 系列芯片中央处理器速度提高了 18%
It starts our next generation of M-Series chips, with an 18% faster CPU
图形处理器速度提高了 35%
35% faster GPU
神经网络引擎速度提高了 40%
40% faster Neural Engine
增加了 50% 内存带宽
and 50% more memory bandwidth
它进一步提升了 M1 芯片绝佳的性能
It takes the amazing performance, capabilities
功能和能效
and efficiency of M1 even further
现在交回给 John
Now, back to John
我们已经开始在为 Mac 搭载新一代 Apple 芯片了
John: The fact that we're already starting our next generation of Apple Silicon
这是件非常了不起的事情
for the Mac is remarkable
那么就让我们来聊聊第一台使用 M2 芯片的 Mac 吧
So now let's talk about the first Mac to get the M2 chip
我们非常高兴地宣布那就是我们最受欢迎的 Mac
We're thrilled that it's our most loved Mac–
MacBook Air
the MacBook Air
用户们喜欢 MacBook Air 出色的性能
Users love MacBook Air for its great performance
便携性和电池续航能力
portability, and battery life
它重新定义了轻薄笔记本电脑品类
It defined the category of thin and light notebooks
而拥有了 M1 芯片之后它又重新定义了轻薄笔记本电脑可以做到的事情
And with M1, it redefined what a thin and light notebook could do
时至今日它比以往任何时候都更受欢迎
Today, it's more popular than ever
事实上 MacBook Air 是世界上最畅销的笔记本电脑
In fact, MacBook Air is the world's best-selling laptop
Apple 芯片能让我们设计出超乎想象的产品
Apple Silicon enables us to design products we never could have imagined
这就是我们为什么会如此兴奋地推出全新 MacBook Air 的原因
which is why we're so excited to introduce an all-new MacBook Air
它完全基于 M2 芯片而重新设计
completely redesigned around M2
这就是它
And here it is
♪♪
这就是由 M2 芯片驱动的新款 MacBook Air
John: This is the new MacBook Air, powered by M2
接下来请 Kristin 来介绍关于它的一切
And to tell you all about it, here's Kristin
新款 MacBook Air 把用户们喜爱 Air 的所有部分
Kristin White: The new MacBook Air takes everything our users love about the Air
都提升到了新的水平
to the next level
上一代 Air 的楔形外观已经变成了
The wedge shape of the previous Air has evolved into a new design
从各个角度看都非常纤薄的全新设计
that's strikingly thin from every angle
全铝金属一体成型机身
The durable, all-aluminum unibody enclosure
手感非常坚固为经久耐用而打造
feels incredibly solid when you hold it and is built to last
这种超薄设计有效地集成了组件
And this remarkably thin design integrates its components so efficiently
与上一代 Air 相比它的体积减少了 20%
that it results in an astonishing 20% reduction in volume over the previous Air
新款 Air 的厚度只有 11.3 毫米
The new Air is just 11.3mm thin
不到半英寸重量仅为 2.7 磅
or under half an inch, and it's only 2.7 pounds
新款 MacBook Air 有四种外观
MacBook Air now comes in four finishes:
银色、深空灰色
Silver, Space Gray
绚丽的星光色和美妙的午夜色
a gorgeous Starlight, and a stunning Midnight
并且 MagSafe 也回来了专为充电使用
And yes, MagSafe is back for dedicated charging
让你插上电源时不用担心
and peace of mind when you're plugged in
还能留出两个雷雳端口
And it keeps the two Thunderbolt ports free
让你自由连接其它各类配件
for connecting to a variety of accessories
还有一个支持高阻抗耳机的耳机插孔
There's also an audio jack with support for high-impedance headphones
这样的全新设计非常便携
This all-new design is incredibly portable
并且它带来了许多新功能
and it's loaded with new features
例如绚丽的 Liquid 视网膜显示屏
starting with a brilliant Liquid Retina display
我们把显示屏进一步向四周扩大直到摄像头周边
We expanded the display closer to the sides and up around the camera
从而为菜单栏腾出空间
to make room for the menu bar
为此创造出了一个更大的 13.6 英寸显示屏它的边框更窄
The result is a larger 13.6-inch display with much thinner borders
可以为用户提供更多屏幕空间让他们能更好地看清屏幕中内容的精彩细节
giving users more screen real estate to view their content in brilliant detail
在 500 尼特下它的亮度比上一代产品增加了 25%
At 500 nits, it's also 25% brighter than before
而且现在的 MacBook Air 支持 10 亿种色彩
And MacBook Air now supports 1 billion colors
所以无论是浏览照片还是观看视频都比从前更加鲜活逼真
so photos and movies look incredibly vibrant
接下来我们来聊聊摄像头
Next, let's talk about the camera
如今拥有一个出色的摄像头已经变得比以往任何时候都更加重要
Having a great camera is more important than ever these days
因此 MacBook Air 配备了全新的 1080p 高清摄像头
So MacBook Air features a new 1080p camera with twice the resolution
它的分辨率和低光性能表现提升至上一代 Air 的两倍
and twice the low-light performance of the previous Air
再结合 M2 芯片先进的图像信号处理器的超强处理能力
Combined with the processing power of M2's advanced image signal processor
你在视频通话中看起来会很棒
you'll look great on video calls
接下去是音频
Next up, audio
为了适应如此纤薄的设计
To fit inside such a thin design, the speakers and mics
扬声器和麦克风完全集成到了键盘和显示屏之间
are completely integrated between the keyboard and display
同时还能提供更好的音频体验
all while delivering an even better audio experience
三麦克风阵列使用先进的波束成形算法捕捉纯净的音频
A three-mic array captures clean audio using advanced beam-forming algorithms
还有四扬声器系统
And there's a four-speaker sound system
能生成优秀的立体声分离度和清晰的人声
that produces amazing stereo separation and vocal clarity
此外还支持通过杜比全景声的音乐和电影
There's also support for immersive Spatial Audio
来提供沉浸式空间音频体验
for music and movies with Dolby Atmos
妙控键盘具有带触控 ID 的全高度功能行
The Magic Keyboard features a full-height function row with Touch ID
当然新的 Air 也配备了
And, of course, the new Air has a spacious
宽大并且业界领先的力度触控板
industry-leading Force Touch trackpad
在性能方面 M2 芯片让一切都更进了一步
And when it comes to performance, M2 takes it even further
在 Photoshop 这样的 app 中使用滤镜和效果的速度
So applying filters and effects in apps like Photoshop
提升最高可达 20%
is up to 20% faster than before
这对于尚未升级到 Apple 芯片的用户来说
and a massive five times faster
这一提升更是快达五倍
for customers that haven't yet upgraded to Apple Silicon
对于在 Final Cut Pro 中编辑复杂时间线这样的密集型工作负载
And for intensive workloads like editing complex timelines in Final Cut Pro
它的性能比上一代提升近 40%
performance is nearly 40% faster than the previous Air
得益于 M2 芯片的强大能效
Thanks to the power efficiency of M2
所有这些功能都内置在一个安静的无风扇设计之中
all these capabilities are built into a silent, fan-less design
即使有了更大的显示屏和更高的性能
And even with a larger display and increased performance
Air 也能提供同样出色的全天候电池续航
the Air delivers the same great all-day battery life
视频播放时间最长可达 18 小时
with up to 18 hours of video playback
在充电方面也有了新的选择
There's also some new charging options
包括一个带有两个 USB-C 端口的紧凑型电源适配器
including a compact power adapter with two USB-C ports
这样你就可以同时为两个设备充电了
so you can charge two devices at once
而且全新的 Air 首次支持
And for the first time
使用现有的 67W 适配器快速充电
the Air supports fast charge with an available 67W adapter
这样你在 30 分钟内就可以把电量充至 50%
So you can charge up to 50% in just 30 minutes
这就是全新的既轻便又强大的 MacBook Air
So that's the all-new, amazingly portable and powerful MacBook Air
它更轻、更薄、更快
It's thinner, lighter, and faster
具有耐用的一体成型机身设计配置了更大的显示屏
with a durable unibody design, bigger display
更好的摄像头具有全天候电池续航时间和四种精美的外观选择
better camera, all-day battery life, and four beautiful finishes
你想要的关于新 MacBook Air 的各个功能都在这里了
It's everything you could want in a new MacBook Air
在我交回给 John 以前让我们看看它的实际效果
Now, before I hand it back to John, let's see it in action
全新 MacBook Air 就位
♪♪
轻薄进化到离谱
MagSafe
♪♪
由M2 芯片强势驱动
妙控键盘
与 iPhone 配合打得好
♪♪
1080p 高清摄像头
最长 18 小时电池续航
♪♪
Liquid 视网膜屏
四扬声器支持空间音频
♪♪
这就是 MacBook Air
我们很高兴能将 M2 芯片用于
John: We're so excited to bring M2 to MacBook Air
世界上最畅销的笔记本电脑 MacBook Air
the world's best-selling laptop
只有使用 Apple 芯片才能打造出如此轻薄的笔记本电脑
Only with Apple Silicon can you build such a thin and light notebook
结合无风扇设计
with a fan-less design
并兼具性能和功能
and this combination of performance and capabilities
但这并不是我们今天要为你带来的全部内容
But that's not all we have for you today
M2 芯片也会用在另一款 Mac 上
M2 is coming to another Mac
而这款 Mac 其实是世界上第二畅销的笔记本电脑
which is actually the world's second-best-selling laptop:
它就是 13 英寸的 MacBook Pro
the 13-inch MacBook Pro
这是我们最便携的 Pro 级别笔记本电脑
It's our most portable pro notebook
用户们喜爱它优秀的性能以及紧凑的设计
and users love the performance it delivers in its compact design
现在有了 M2 芯片你就能从同样出色的外形设计中
Now with M2, you get even more capabilities
获得更多功能
in the same great form factor
凭借更快的 8 核中央处理器和 10 核图形处理器
With a faster 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU
在 Affinity Photo 这样的 app 中处理 RAW 图像的速度
working with RAW images in apps like Affinity Photo
比上一代快了几乎 40%
is nearly 40% faster than the previous generation
如果是从非 Apple 芯片的型号升级而来
And over three times faster
速度则会比之前快三倍多
if you're upgrading from a model without Apple Silicon
玩 Baldur’s Gate III 这样的图形密集型游戏
And playing graphics intensive games like Baldur's Gate III
速度也比之前的 13 英寸 Pro 提高了将近 40%
is also nearly 40% faster than the previous 13-inch Pro
这台 MacBook Pro 配备了主动散热系统
With an active cooling system, the MacBook Pro is designed
从而保持专业级别的性能输出
to sustain its pro performance
并且得益于 M2 芯片它也支持最高 24GB 的统一内存
And thanks to M2, it also supports up to 24GB of unified memory
因为内存带宽增加了 50%
Along with 50% more memory bandwidth
使得处理多任务和大型素材的工作也变得超级流畅
multitasking and working with large assets is super fluid
借助 M2 芯片的媒体处理引擎中对 ProRes 的编解码支持
With support for ProRes encode and decode in M2's media engine
你把视频项目转化为 ProRes 的速度
you can convert your video projects to ProRes
可以达到比上一代快大约三倍
nearly three times faster than before
MacBook Pro 的电池续航时间也非常长
MacBook Pro also delivers phenomenal battery life
视频播放时间长达 20 小时
with up to 20 hours of video playback
这就是功能强大的 13 英寸 MacBook Pro
So that's the powerful 13-inch MacBook Pro
配备了性能优秀的 M2 芯片 ProRes 加速功能
With the incredible performance of M2, ProRes acceleration
高达 24GB 的内存和长达 20 小时的电池续航
up to 24GB of memory, and up to 20 hours of battery life
我们最便携的 Pro 级别笔记本电脑变得更出色了
our most portable Pro notebook gets even better
最新的 Air 和 Pro 也都符合我们的环保目标
Both the Air and the Pro also support our environmental goals
它们的许多组件都使用 100% 再生稀土元素
They use 100% recycled rare earth elements in many components
不含多种有害物质
are free of numerous harmful substances
并且符合 Apple 对能源效率的高标准
and meet Apple's high standards for energy efficiency
全新的 MacBook Air 起售价为 $1199
The all-new MacBook Air starts at $1199
教育优惠价仅为 $1099
and just $1099 for education
功能强大的 13 英寸 MacBook Pro 起售价为 $1299
The powerful 13-inch MacBook Pro starts at $1299
教育优惠价为 $1199
and $1199 for education
它们下个月就会上市
And they'll be available next month
配备 M1 芯片的 MacBook Air 将继续保留并保持起售价为 $999
And the MacBook Air with M1 stays in the lineup at $999
教育优惠价仅为 $899
and just $899 for education
我们很高兴能把 M2 芯片引入两款世界上最受欢迎的笔记本电脑
We're thrilled to bring M2 to the world's two most popular laptops
MacBook Air 和 13 英寸 MacBook Pro
the MacBook Air and 13-inch MacBook Pro
它们和搭载 M1 Pro 和 M1 Max 芯片的
And they join the even more powerful 14 and 16-inch MacBook Pro
甚至更强大的 14 英寸和 16 英寸 MacBook Pro 一起
with M1 Pro and M1 Max
完善了我们有史以来最出色的 Mac 产品线
to round out the most amazing lineup of Macs we've ever offered
并延续了我们对 Mac 惊人的创新速度
and continue our tremendous pace of innovation for the Mac
现在交回给 Craig
Now, back to Craig
我们非常期待
Craig: We're really excited about these new Macs
使用新一代 Apple 芯片的 Mac
with the next generation of Apple Silicon
而推动这种体验的强大软件就是 macOS
And the powerful software that drives the experience is macOS
那让我们来聊聊这次的更新
So let's talk about what's new
跳起来！蹲下！
Kyle: Jump! Sit!
怎么了 Craig?
Craig?
对不起 Kyle 我走错门了！
Craig: Sorry, Kyle. Wrong door
♪♪
macOS 在我们的生活中发挥着重要的作用
macOS plays a critical role in our lives
在我们工作的时候与同事、家人和朋友合作交流的时候
as we work, collaborate with colleagues, family, and friends
在我们规划重要事情的时候
create and organize what's important to us
以及更多其它场合
and so much more
今年我们专注于把你们在 macOS 做的核心事务变得更好
This year, we focused on making the core things you do with macOS even better
通过提供新方法让用户获得生产力
delivering new ways to be productive and take advantage
并利用和其他设备连续互通时所获得的能力
of the capability of your other devices with Continuity
那么我们应该把它叫做什么呢
So what should we call it?
这就要提到 Apple Marketing 团队
Well, that brings us to the latest exploits
最新的开拓之旅了
of Apple's crack product marketing team
自从给 M1 和 M2 芯片成功命名后他们一路高歌猛进
They've been absolutely riding high since their naming coup on M1 and M2
当然他们已经精疲力尽了
and needless to say, they were exhausted
但是在 Monterey 进行了三个月的必要的修养后
But after their requisite three-month rejuvenation retreat in Monterey
他们的精力已经完全恢复了
with their chakras now in complete alignment
团队再次挤进了他们的小巴车沿着 1 号公路向南行驶
the team once again piled into their macOS naming microbus
继续着他们为 macOS 命名的旅程
and wove their way down Highway 1
追随着五彩缤纷的加州野花
Chasing the vibrant display of colorful California wildflowers
他们终于在迷人的海浪
they finally came to rest
与茂盛的冲积平原交汇处找到了休息之地
where stunning surf meets lush alluvial plains
这就是美丽的 Ventura
in beautiful Ventura
macOS Ventura 让我们使用 Mac 的方式变得更丰富了
macOS Ventura enriches so many of the ways we use our Macs
那么让我们仔细来了解一下
So let's jump in
Mac 体验的关键在于帮你变得更有生产力也更有创造力
A key part of the Mac experience is helping you be productive and creative
这也常常意味着你需要一次打开很多窗口
which can often mean having a lot of windows open at once
可当窗口越来越多时也会变得越来越应接不暇
And the more you do, the more overwhelming this can become
我们都想要达到一个完美的平衡
We all want the perfect mix–
既要专注于自己的工作不被分心
to focus on our work without distractions
又希望在各种任务之间轻松切换
and to easily move between tasks
今年我们有了一种能让一切都自动变得井井有条
This year, we have a new way to automatically keep everything organized
也能让你快速访问各个窗口的新方法
and give you quick access to your windows
这就是台前调度
It's called Stage Manager
我们来看看它是怎么发挥作用的
Let's see how it works
当你用 Mac 工作时常常会发现
When you're working on the Mac, it's really easy
自己同时打开了许多窗口
to find yourself with lots of open windows
Mac 有调度中心这样的优秀工具
Now, the Mac has great tools like Mission Control
能帮你找到你需要的窗口
to help you find the window that you're looking for
但是有这么多打开的窗口
but with so many open windows
可能会让工作区域不可避免地显得杂乱无章
it can feel like you never really escape all the clutter
有了台前调度你就可以心无旁骛地专注在你正在用的 app 上
With Stage Manager, you can focus on the app you're using
不会被分心了
without the distractions
而且它使用起来很简单
and it's easy to get started
现在让我们从控制中心启动台前调度
Let's activate Stage Manager from Control Center
你会看到它自动把我所有的窗口都排列在了屏幕一边
As you see, it automatically arranges all my windows for me off to the side
而台前调度把我正在使用的 app 放在了屏幕最前方的中间位置
and puts the app I'm currently working with front and center
当我点开新 app 的时候
When I bring forward a different app
比如我点击了程序坞里的邮件 app
like clicking on Mail here in the Dock
你就会看到邮件 app 在屏幕前方最中间的位置打开了
you'll see that it's brought to the stage
而 Safari 浏览器就被优雅地挪到左边
and Safari gracefully moves over to the left
与其他我近期使用过的 app 放在一起
with my other recent apps
当我再次点击 Safari 浏览器的时候你可以看到它重新占据了舞台
When I click on Safari, it retakes the stage
而邮件 app 退到了左边
and Mail moves back to the left
你会注意到
You'll notice that for an app with multiple open windows
在处理打开了许多窗口的 app 时比如这里的 Pages 文稿
like Pages here, Stage Manager gathers all the windows together
台前调度把这些窗口都聚集在了一起
in a single pile
只要点击一下最上面的窗口就会打开
When I click, I get the top one
如果我想打开别的窗口
and if I want a different window, I can cycle through them
也可以通过点击来让它们循环
just by clicking
这真的是很方便
It's really convenient
当然就像你对 Mac 的设想一样
Of course, just as you would expect on a Mac
我也可以让窗口重叠放置并且同时打开许多个 app
I can have overlapping windows and multiple apps open at the same time too
把 app 组合在一起真的很容易
It's really easy to group apps together
我只需要把备忘录拖过来和 Pages 文稿的窗口放在一起就可以了
Here I'll just drag in Notes and pair it with my Pages window
当我工作需要用到一组 app 时
This is so great when I'm working on projects
这样的功能就可以派上大用场了
that involve a specific group of windows
比如我用这 3 个 app 来计划一趟旅行
like planning a trip with these three apps here
而当我回到我之前在用的一组 app 时
And if I go back to my previous group
台前调度依然保留了
Stage Manager keeps my windows arranged
所有窗口原本的顺序
just as I left them
我很喜欢这样的工作方式
I love working this way
当然就像许多 Mac 用户一样
Of course, like many Mac users
我会经常想要访问桌面上的文件
I often want to get at files on my desktop
有了台前调度这一切就变得都比之前更容易了
and with Stage Manager, we've made that easier than ever
我正在处理这个 Final Cut 项目
I'm working on this Final Cut project
这时我想拖入几个文件
and I want to pull in a couple of files
只要点击桌面我的窗口就会把桌面空出来
With just a click on my desktop, my windows clear the stage
而我的文件就会出现
and my files are revealed
这样我就可以选取这些标题图形
Now I can grab these title graphics
把它们拖拽到我的 Final Cut 窗口上
and drag them over to my Final Cut window
我只要把它们放在这里
I'll just drop them in right here
就一切搞定
and boom
这就是对使用台前调度进行多任务处理的简单介绍
So that's a quick look at multitasking with Stage Manager
Mac 体验中另一个能帮你完成更多工作的功能就是聚焦
Another part of the Mac experience that helps you do more is Spotlight
今年我们会发布这方面的重大更新它将为我们带来更加一致也更加强大的体验
This year we have a big update that delivers a more consistent
并贯穿于各个平台
and powerful experience across our platforms
聚焦适用于各种各样的任务
Spotlight is great for doing all kinds of things
比如可以用来快速打开 app 或者开始搜索等
like quickly launching an app or starting a search
现在你可以通过快速查看来了解搜索结果
And now you can peek at a result in Quick Look
并且只需要轻按空格键就可以
with a tap on the space bar
聚焦现在也可以用来查找照片
Spotlight can now also find images from your photo library
从你的照片图库整个系统以及网络上来查找
across the system, and on the web
使用实况文本你也可以搜索图片中的文字
And using Live Text, you can search the text inside the image
还可以直接通过聚焦启动计时器
You can also take actions like starting a timer
或者运行快捷方式等
or running a shortcut right from Spotlight
这也变成了获取信息的绝佳方式
It's also a great way to get information
现在它会利用整个窗口来展示更丰富的搜索结果
now leveraging the full window for richer results
搜索音乐人的时候你会看到他们的专辑关键信息、相关新闻以及其它信息
For musicians, you'll see their albums, key facts, news, and more
聚焦也非常适合用来搜索电影电视节目和演员
It's also great for movies, TV shows, and actors
商家还有体育运动
businesses, and sports
直接从聚焦开展操作的功能和丰富的搜索结果
Rich results and the ability to take actions right from Spotlight
也将会出现在 iOS 和 iPadOS 上
are also coming to iOS and iPadOS
说到 iOS
Now, speaking of iOS, we wanted to make Spotlight even easier
我们想让访问聚焦更加容易
to discover and access
所以我们把它添加到了主屏幕的底部
so we added it right to the bottom of the Home Screen
只需要轻点一下你就可以用聚焦启动 app
With just a tap, you can use Spotlight to launch an app
查找联系人或者开始搜索
find a contact, or start a search
这些更新让聚焦更高效更快速地
These updates make Spotlight more productive
帮你找到需要的内容
helping you find what you're looking for faster
接下来让我们来聊一个我们很多人每天都会用来沟通交流的 app
Next, let's turn to an app that many of us use to communicate every day
让 Darin 来告诉你们更多
To take you through it, here's Darin
这个 app 当然是邮件 app
Darin Adler: Of course, we're talking about Mail
邮件 app 是我们中许多人交流沟通的核心方式
Mail is central to how so many of us communicate
今年我们带来了许多能帮助你提高工作效率的重大更新
This year, we have great updates that will help you be more productive
首先就是一些被要求最多的功能
starting with some highly-requested features
撤销发送可以让你在发送邮件之后的片刻还能撤回邮件
Undo send lets you pull an email back a few moments after hitting Send
定时发送能让你的邮件在最完美的时间到达收件人
Scheduled send, so your emails arrive at the perfect moment
跟进建议会自动提醒你跟进这封邮件
Follow-up suggestions will automatically remind you to follow up
如果你的邮件没有收到回复
if you haven't received a response
稍后提醒我这个功能可以让你轻松回到相关的信件
And Remind Me makes it easy to come back to a message
在特定日期和时间
at a particular date and time
接下来我们来聊聊搜索功能
Next, let's talk Search
这是多年来我们对邮件 app 中的搜索功能做的最大一次改造
This is the biggest overhaul of Search in Mail we've done in years
我们利用了最新最先进的技术
leveraging the latest state-of-the-art techniques
来提供更准确更全面的结果
to deliver more accurate and complete results
点进搜索的时候
When you click Search, you'll see recently shared documents
你会看到最近分享的文件、链接等等
links, and more
开始打字之后
The moment you start typing
每打出一个字就能立即看到建议的结果
with each letter, you instantly see suggestions
如果你打错了字搜索也能比你更快一步
If you make a typo, Search is one step ahead
只显示正确拼写的结果
only showing results for the correct spelling
如果搜索发现了同义词它也会显示意义相同的结果
And if Search knows a synonym, it'll look for that too
这些新功能也会引入 iPadOS 和 iOS
And all these new features are also coming to iPadOS and iOS
这就是关于邮件 app 的更新
And that's Mail
接下来我们要介绍的是另外一个我们大多数人都会在上面花很久时间的 app
Next up is another app most of us spend a ton of time in every day:
Safari 浏览器
Safari
在 macOS Ventura 系统中 Safari 浏览器的速度首屈一指
With macOS Ventura, Safari is the world's fastest browser
即使最复杂的网站也能瞬间呈现在你眼前
rendering the most complex websites with incredible speed
Safari 浏览器是 Mac 上最高能效的浏览器
Safari is the most power-efficient browser on Mac
与其它浏览器相比充电一次可以在 Safari 上完成更多操作
letting you do more on a single charge than any other browser
当然 Safari 浏览器也是保护你网络隐私的先行者
And of course, Safari is a trailblazer in protecting your privacy on the web
其中的智能防跟踪功能
with features like Intelligent Tracking Protection
和隐私报告在时刻发挥它们的作用
and Privacy Report
Safari 浏览器在引入关键的网络技术以提升每个人的网络体验方面
Safari has a legacy of introducing key web technologies
有着悠久的历史
that elevate the web experience for everyone
Safari 浏览器对 HTML5 的开创性支持优化了网络上的视频体验
Safari's pioneering support for HTML5 transformed the video experience
让视频播放的质量更高还增加了电池续航时间
on the web, resulting in higher-quality playback and increased battery life
并且 Safari 浏览器持续为网络开发者
And Safari continues to deliver support for the latest web technologies
提供最新网络技术和标准
and standards for web developers
包括去年所添加的这些更新
including all of these added in just the last year
例如更流畅的网络动画新的浏览器扩展类型
like more fluid web animations, new browser extension types
以及对新的推送通知标准的支持
and support for the push notifications standards
这些更新为我们的用户带来了更身临其境也更引人入胜的网络内容
These enable more immersive and engaging web content for our users
现在 Safari 浏览器还带来了能与其他人分享你最爱内容的新方法
And now Safari has a new way to share your favorite content with others
共享标签页组
with Shared Tab Groups
无论你是在和朋友计划旅行还是和你的伴侣选购沙发
Whether you're planning a trip with friends or shopping for a couch
都可以把所有的标签页分享在一处
with your partner, you can share all the tabs in one place
而如果他们也找到了不错的内容他们也可以添加标签页
And when they find something great, they can add tabs too
你可以实时查看你的朋友们正在浏览的标签页
You can see which tabs your friends are looking at live
并且通过内置的协作功能你们也能
and using built-in collaboration, you can easily connect in real time
通过信息 app 和 FaceTime 通话来实时联络
over Messages or FaceTime
和亲友共同探索网络世界变得非常容易
It's so easy to discover the web together
接下来我们还有能让网络空间变得更安全的新方法
And next, we have a new way to make the web a safer place
我们依靠密码来保护我们最隐私的账号
We rely on passwords to protect our most private accounts
虽然 Safari 浏览器可以帮用户创建最强的密码
While Safari helps users create the strongest passwords possible
但仍有一些方法可以让账户遭到破坏
there are still ways accounts can be compromised
黑客会用网络钓鱼这样的社交工程技巧
Hackers can use social engineering techniques like phishing
来诱使用户交出密码
to trick users into giving up passwords
他们还可以直接破解网站
They can also breach a website directly
以获取储存在服务器上的所有密码
to get access to all the passwords stored on its server
这就是为什么我们打造了
That's why we've helped create a next generation credential
更安全、更简便
that's more secure, easier to use
并且以替代密码为目标的新一代身份验证信息
and aims to replace passwords for good
我们叫它通行密钥
We call them passkeys
通行密钥使用了强大的加密技术
Passkeys use powerful cryptographic techniques
和设备内置的生物识别技术来保护账户的安全
and the biometrics built into your device to keep accounts safe
只要使用触控 ID 或者面容 ID 进行身份验证
To create a passkey, just use TouchID
你就可以轻松创建通行密钥
or FaceID to authenticate, and you're done
用户创建通行密钥的时候会产生一个独一无二的数字钥匙
When users create a passkey, a unique digital key is created
它只能用于创建它的网站
that only works for the site it was created for
通行密钥是无法被盗用的
Passkeys can't be phished
由于通行密钥永远不会离开你的设备
Since the passkey never leaves your devices
所以黑客无法诱使你把它分享在虚假网站上
hackers can't trick you into sharing it on a fake website
并且因为网络服务器上没有储存任何私密信息通行密钥也不会被泄露
And passkeys can't be leaked because nothing secret is kept on a web server
我们设计的通行密钥可以在 app 里轻松使用就像在网页上一样
We've designed passkeys to work in apps as easily as they do on the web
用 iCloud 钥匙串就可以把通行密钥在你的 Apple 设备上安全同步
Passkeys are securely synced across Apple devices using iCloud Keychain
并且可以在 Mac iPhone、iPad 和 Apple TV 上即时使用
and are instantly available on Mac
iPhone, iPad, and Apple TV
我们还和 FIDO alliance 中
We've been working with industry leaders
包括谷歌和微软等合作
in the FIDO alliance including Google and Microsoft
以保证通行密钥能在不同平台间无缝使用
to ensure that passkeys work seamlessly cross-platform
有了通行密钥即使面对非 Apple 设备
With a passkey, you'll be able to walk up to a non-Apple device
你也可以用你的 iPhone 登录网站或 app
and sign in to a website or app using just your iPhone
这种脱离密码的转型并不会一蹴而就
The transition away from passwords will be a journey
我们期待和开发者们协同合作共同创造一个无密码的未来
and we look forward to working with developers on the password-less future
这些就是关于 Safari 浏览器的更新
And that's Safari
现在交回到 Craig
Now back over to you, Craig
我们相信这些对邮件 app 和 Safari 浏览器的更新
Craig: We think these updates to Mail and Safari
可以帮你提高工作效率
will help you be productive and browse the web
并让你以更安全的新方式浏览网页
in new and safer ways
下面让我们来聊聊有趣的游戏部分
Next, let's have some fun and talk about gaming
我们正处在一个交叉点上
We're at a point where two things are really coming together
一方面 Apple 芯片改变了一切
First, Apple Silicon has changed everything
它把所有 Mac 的图形性能都提升到了新的高度
It's taking the graphics performance of every new Mac to new heights
即使是要求最高的游戏在 Mac 上也能轻松运行
giving Macs the power to run the most demanding games, with ease
另一方面 Mac 的销量节节升高
Second, the Mac is more popular than ever
所以对于游戏开发者来说 Mac 带来了大量且不断增加的机会
and it's a huge and fast-growing opportunity for game developers
而且我们采用了统一的芯片架构
And since we have a unified silicon architecture spanning from iPhone and iPad
从 iPhone 和 iPad 直到 M1 Ultra 芯片
all the way up to M1 Ultra
游戏开发人员可以在整条产品线上
game developers can scale the quality and performance of their titles
扩展他们游戏的质量和性能
across the entire line
另一个关于游戏体验的关键部分是为其提供支持的软件
Another key part of a great gaming experience is the software that powers it
这部分的更新就请 Jeremy 来告诉你
To tell you what's new, here's Jeremy
我们一直在对 Metal 做出改进
Jeremy Sandmel: We continue to improve Metal
在我们所有的软件平台上都是这项软件技术
It's the software that powers hardware-accelerated graphics
驱动着硬件加速带来的图形处理
on all our platforms
现在 Metal 3 带来的新功能
And now, Metal 3 brings new features that will unleash
将源源不断地释放 Apple 芯片的全部潜力
the full potential of Apple Silicon for years to come
在最高的分辨率和画质下游戏体验会非常棒
Gaming at maximum resolution and quality looks awesome
为了帮助游戏开发人员提高图形性能
And to help game developers increase the performance of realistic
带来更加逼真也更沉浸式的体验我们推出了 MetalFX 上采样
and immersive graphics, we're introducing MetalFX Upscaling
让开发人员可以更快速地渲染丰富而视觉复杂的图形
which enables developers to render rich, visually complex scenes even faster
它通过渲染较小且计算量较少的帧来工作
It works by rendering smaller, less compute-intensive frames
然后使用高质量的空间放大和时间抗锯齿
and then applies high-quality spatial upscaling and temporal anti-aliasing
效果非常棒
And it's so cool
即将在今年晚些时候登陆 Mac 的 No Man’s Sky
No Man's Sky, coming to Mac later this year
就是第一批使用 MetalFX 上采样技术的游戏之一
will be one of the first games to use MetalFX Upscaling
它的帧率有所增加能给人带来反应灵敏的感觉并且看起来非常漂亮
The frame rate increases, giving you that responsive feel, and it looks beautiful
我们带来改进的另一个方面是游戏加载
Another area we're improving is game loading
游戏通过使用更丰富的纹理和更多几何细节
Games continue to push the boundaries and appear more realistic than ever before
不断突破边界变得更加逼真
by using richer textures and more geometric detail
而这也造成了更长的加载时间
which can take a while to load
所以 Metal 3 添加了新的快速资源加载 API
So Metal 3 adds a new fast resource loading API
它通过提供从存储到统一内存系统的更直接路径
that minimizes wait time by providing a more direct path
来最大限度地减少等待时间
from storage to the unified memory system
这样图形处理器就能更快速地
so the GPU can more quickly access high-quality textures
访问高质量纹理和缓冲区而无需等待
and buffers without waiting
Metal 3 和 Apple 芯片可以实现更沉浸式的视觉效果
Metal 3 and Apple Silicon enable even more immersive visuals
更好的性能和更快的加载速度
faster performance, and quicker loading
这的确为在 Mac 上玩游戏带来了新时代
This really is a new day for gaming on the Mac
当然不能光听我们自己说
But don't take our word for it
让我们听听来自创造了广受好评的
Let's hear from the team that has created
Resident Evil Village 游戏团队的意见吧
the acclaimed Resident Evil Village
我们非常高兴它即将登陆 Mac
We are so excited it's coming to the Mac
接下来请 Capcom 高级技术研究部的经理
To tell you more, we are delighted to introduce Ijuin-san
Ijuin 先生来为你介绍更多吧
manager of Capcom's Advanced Technical Research Division
♪♪
Resident Evil Village 一经公布就成为了一种定义游戏类型的游戏
为玩家带来了激动人心的有趣体验
时至今日这个系列依然在同类游戏中最受欢迎
所以我们非常高兴能为
搭载 Apple 芯片的 Mac 产品线带来我们最新的游戏
得益于 Apple 芯片 Mac 如今具有超棒的性能
是一个出众的游戏平台
并且凭借我们对新 Metal 3 的支持
从 MacBook Air 到速度极快的 Mac Studio
我们的游戏在 Apple 芯片上大放异彩
你可以看到我们可以非常流畅地在这些美到惊心动魄的场景中移动
我们在这里使用了高质量纹理几何图形和复杂的着色器
借助 MetalFX 上采样
我们可以在整个产品线上呈现绝佳的高分辨率视觉效果
MacBook Air 够以 1080p 轻松运行
Mac Studio 也可以带来的惊人 4K 体验
从前只有高性能游戏主机和游戏电脑
可以做到这一点
但现在我们把它引入了每一台由 Apple 芯片驱动的 Mac 上
我们对这些全新 Mac 能够实现的真实感惊叹不已
这些全新 Mac 产品可以毫不费力地处理好我们交给它们的任何任务
这真是不可思议！
我们迫不及待地想把这款游戏交到世界各地的 Mac 游戏玩家手中
请期待今年晚些时候发布的 Mac 版本的 Resident Evil Village 吧
这就是我今天全部的分享
非常感谢
现在让我们回到 Craig
感谢 Ijuin 先生的发言
Craig: Thank you, Ijuin-san
接下来我们要聊的是连续互通
Next, let's talk about Continuity
连续互通能让你在使用不同设备时拥有无缝衔接的体验
Continuity is all about giving you a seamless experience across devices
通用控制、隔空播放和接力等功能
Features like Universal Control, AirPlay, and Handoff
可以让你始终根据当下的情况使用最合适的设备
allow you to always use the right device for the moment
而今天我们要将接力功能扩展到 FaceTime 通话
And today, we're extending Handoff to FaceTime
想象一下你正在用 iPhone 进行 FaceTime 通话
Now picture this: you answer a FaceTime call on your iPhone
此时你并没有在桌前
while you're away from your desk
而当你到家之后将 iPhone 靠近 Mac 时
When you get home and bring your iPhone up close to your Mac
你的 Mac 就会自动识别出 iPhone 上的通话
your Mac automatically recognizes the call on your iPhone
这时你就可以让通话无缝切换到 Mac 上
and you can move it to your Mac seamlessly
通话的视图也会变得更大
giving you a bigger view to continue the conversation
你的所有设备都能从任何方向接力你的通话
You can handoff calls in any direction between your devices
所以你始终都能用最合适的设备来继续通话
so you'll always be able to join the call from the right one
关于连续互通我们还有另一个好消息
We also have exciting news about another Continuity feature
那就是它会把你最好的相机和 Mac 上最大的显示屏相匹配
which pairs the best camera you own with the large displays on Mac
很多时候我们需要用到 Mac 的摄像头
We spend a lot of time in front of our Macs with our cameras on
而视频摄像头已经变成了我们工作、学习和娱乐中不可或缺的一部分
Our webcams have become an integral part of work, school, and play
现在连续互通相机
And now, with Continuity Camera
支持将 iPhone 作为你的视频摄像头了
you can use iPhone as your webcam
iPhone 相机系统的先进功能
It's powered by the advanced capabilities of the iPhone camera system
可以做到一般视频摄像头无法做到的事情
letting you do things that were never before possible with a webcam
我来向你展示一下它是如何运行的
Let me show you how it works
首先我把 iPhone 放在这个支架上
Now, I'm just gonna pop this stand on my iPhone
让它放置到我的显示器上
and attach it to my display
然后启动 FaceTime 通话
Let's launch FaceTime
你会看到我的 Mac 自动检测到了 iPhone
You can see my Mac automatically detects my iPhone
然后使用了 iPhone 的摄像头
and uses it as the camera
我甚至都不必唤醒我的 iPhone
I don't even have to wake up my iPhone
而且这一切都可以无线完成不需要任何插拔
This all works wirelessly so there's nothing to plug in
那就让我们试试这个功能给设计工作室的朋友打个电话吧
So to try this out, let's call a friend in the design studio
嗨 Craig！
Johnnie Manzari: Hi, Craig!
嘿 Johnnie！
Craig: Hey, Johnnie!
你愿意帮我演示一下连续互通相机吗？
Are you up for helping me give a demo of Continuity Camera?
当然  我现在就在用这个功能通过我的 iPhone
Johnnie: Sure, I'm using it right now
和我的 Pro Display XDR 显示器
with my iPhone and Pro Display XDR
关于连续互通相机我很喜欢的一点就是它的人物居中功能
You know, one thing I love about Continuity Camera is Center Stage
我可以四处移动而人物居中功能会让我一直处于画面中
I can move around and Center Stage will keep me in the frame
我经常把它和人像模式一起使用
I'll frequently pair that with Portrait Mode
用虚化效果模糊我的背景
to blur the background with that beautiful boca
是的我真的很喜欢 iPad 上的这些功能
Craig: Yeah, I've loved having these features on my iPad
现在我们可以在任何 Mac 上使用它了实在是太好了
and it's great that we can now use them with any Mac
当然
Johnnie: For sure
还有一个大家会喜欢的新功能那就是摄影室灯光
A new one people are gonna love is Studio Light
来看看这个
Check this out
它可以让我的面部变亮而让背景变暗
It brightens my face and darkens the background
看起来真不错
Craig: Hey, that looks great
就好像你开了环形补光灯一样
It's almost like you have a ring-light
它非常适合在我光线条件较差的时候使用
Johnnie: It is perfect for tough lighting conditions
看起来就像我坐在窗前一样
like if I'm ever sitting in front of a window
现在我想展示我最喜欢的新功能桌面视图
Okay, now I wanna show my favorite new feature, Desk View
你可以看到我桌面上的工作
You can see the work that's on my desk
而且还能让我也出现在画面中
and it keeps me in the picture
这个功能实在是很棒
It is amazing
你看
Take a look
它看起来就像我安装了专用的俯视角摄像头一样
It looks like I have a dedicated overhead camera
但这其实是桌面视图功能产生出的两个视图
but this is Desk View creating both of these views
使用了 iPhone 上的超广角摄像头
from the one ultra-wide camera on my iPhone
和非常强大的图像处理技术
using some very powerful image processing
我甚至都不用调整我的手机
I didn't even need to adjust my phone
桌面视图非常适合用来给我的团队分享新设计
Desk View's gonna be great for sharing new designs with my team
我甚至可以用它给我的侄子展示新的纸牌技巧
I can even use it to show my nephew a new card trick
这真的特别酷
Craig: This is gonna be so cool
好的 Johnnie 谢谢你为我们带来的演示
Well, hey, Johnnie, thanks for helping us give the quick demo
不客气我们一会儿再聊
Johnnie: No problem. I'll talk to you later
除了 FaceTime 通话你还可以用连续互通相机
Craig: In addition to FaceTime, you can use Continuity Camera
和 macOS 上的任何视频会议 app 配合使用
with any macOS videoconferencing app
比如 Zoom、Teams、Webex 等
like Zoom, Teams, Webex, and more
我们正在和 Belkin 合作会为用户带来精美的手机支架
And we're working with Belkin to offer beautiful stands
以恰好的高度和角度固定你的 iPhone
to hold your iPhone at the perfect height and angle
它们会在今年晚些时候上市
These will be available later this year
而且你们中的很多人同时拥有一台 Mac 和一部 iPhone
And since so many of you with a Mac already have an iPhone
所以这些新功能在你已经拥有的设备上就能实现
these great capabilities come with the devices you already own
这就是连续互通的魔力
That's the magic of Continuity
以上这些就是我们的 macOS Ventura
And that's macOS Ventura
这是一个功能丰富的版本它带来了管理窗口的新工具
a feature-packed release that brings new tools for managing windows
为邮件 app、 Safari 浏览器和游戏带来了智能的新功能
smart new features for Mail, Safari, and games
还有神奇的连续互通新功能
and magical new Continuity features
下面我们要谈到的是 iPadOS
Now let's turn to iPadOS
♪♪
我们对 iPadOS 的愿景是
Our vision for iPadOS
创造一种基于 iOS 优点的独特体验
is to create a distinct experience
that's built on the best of iOS
例如保证安全性具有移动性和直观的触控优先界面
like security, mobility, and an intuitive touch-first interface
它拥有 macOS 的强大功能
with powerful capabilities from macOS
比如多任务处理和触控板支持
like multitasking and trackpad support
并与 iPad 独有的功能相结合例如 Apple Pencil
combined with features like Apple Pencil that are uniquely iPad
所有这些特点结合在一起就组成了我们最全能的设备
All of this comes together to deliver our most versatile device
今年的 iPadOS 16 是一个重要的版本
This year in iPadOS 16, we have a big release
它将进一步提升 iPad 的这种多用性
that's going to take this versatility even further
首先就是你已经在 iOS 和 macOS 中听过的一系列功能
Starting with a host of features that you heard about earlier in iOS and macOS
这些功能也会适用于 iPad
that are going to be great on iPad
例如共享图库
like Shared Photo Library
共享标签页组 Safari 浏览器中的通行密钥
Shared Tab Groups and Passkeys in Safari
还有邮件 app 中的重大更新
and a big update to Mail
我们也会把天气功能引入 iPad
We're also bringing Weather to iPad
充分利用漂亮的显示屏和出色的动画效果
taking full advantage of the stunning display with beautiful animations
比如这些缓缓移动的云
like these gently moving clouds
还有大雪和大雨的画面
heavy snowfall, and driving rain
并且所有模块都可以通过轻点来访问详细信息
And all of these modules are tappable to access detailed information
而针对开发人员我们也会发布 WeatherKit
And for developers, we're announcing WeatherKit
这样他们就可以把天气信息内置在他们的 app 中了
so they can build weather into their apps
iPadOS 16 也包含了与他人协作的新方式
iPadOS 16 also includes new ways to collaborate with others
功能更强大的 app
more capable apps, and new features for Pro users
还有为专业用户提供的能充分利用 M1 芯片的新功能
that take advantage of the power of the M1 chip
那我们就先来了解协作
So let's start with collaboration
它常常从信息 app 开始
which often begins in Messages
你被要求传输一份文件
when you're asked to pass along a document
当然你可以发送一份副本
Of course, you could send a copy
但现在你也可以在用共享表单发送文件时
but now you can also instantly kick off a collaboration
立即启动协作
when you send something with the Share Sheet
这个功能把在整个系统中发起协作
This makes initiating collaboration across the system
变得像发送链接一样容易
as easy as sending a link
并且意味着你只需要轻轻一点就能与协作者发起对话了
and means a conversation with your collaborators is always just a tap away
我来向你展示一下它是怎样操作的
Let me show you how it works
那就让我们点进信息 app
So let's tap in to Messages
我一直在和团队讨论一个接下来的场外活动
I've been talking to the team about an upcoming offsite
我们在利用这次谈话确定细节
and we've been using this conversation to figure out the details
现在看起来 Lopp 发来了一条信息
Now, it looks like a message just came in from Lopp
他想要了解最新的消息
and he wants to catch up on the latest
在这边的 Pages 文稿里面我记录搜集了我们的想法
Over here in Pages, I've been collecting our ideas
我想要和小组成员们分享这些文稿
I want to share this with the group
在过去我点击分享的时候
In the past, when I'd tap Share
最终分享的是一份副本
I'd end up sharing a copy
现在你会注意到我可以直接在这里发起协作
But now, you'll notice I can start collaboration right here
而且最好的一点就是我不需要把大家的名字或者邮件地址
And what's great is, I don't need to type in a bunch of names
都打出来
or email addresses
只要我选择一个信息组每个人就自动被添加进来了
When I select a Messages group, everyone gets added automatically
让我们把文件发给大家吧
Let's go ahead and send it
这让你可以更加容易地与已经在沟通的人协作
This makes it way easier to collaborate with people
you're already communicating with
每个人都可以立即加入并且开始编辑
Everyone can immediately join and start making edits
就像你在这里看到的一样
like the ones you see here
而在信息 app 的对话中
And back in the Messages conversation
我甚至能收到我可能错过的任何修改的通知
I even get a notice of any changes I might have missed
当你用这种方式协作时
When you collaborate this way, your document is connected
你的文件就会和对话相关联
to the conversation
小组会在工具栏中出现
The group appears in the toolbar
我可以直接从这里开始交流
and I can kick off communication right from here
我可以随时回到信息 app 中的对话
I can get back to the messages conversation
或者发起 FaceTime 通话
or initiate a FaceTime call
让我们给小组成员发起通话试试看
Let's go ahead and call the group
嗨大家好！
Hey, everyone!
嗨 Craig！
Michael Lopp: Hey, Craig
嗨我看到你们有几个人在文件里
Craig: Hey, I saw that a few of you were in the document
你们对场外活动还有其它想法吗
Does anyone have any other ideas for the offsite?
是的我一直在考虑并且收集了一些标签页
Lopp: Yeah, I've been thinking about it, and I've been collecting a few tabs
我现在就从 Safari 浏览器把它们分享给你
I'm gonna share them right now with you in Safari
谢谢 Lopp
Craig: Thanks, Lopp
今年你可以直接在 FaceTime 通话里开始与小组协作
This year, you can start collaborating with the group right in FaceTime
你可以看到 Lopp 刚才邀请我在 Safari 浏览器的一组标签页中协作
You can see that Lopp just invited me to collaborate on a set of tabs in Safari
我现在要接受他的邀请
I'm gonna go ahead and accept his invite
然后我就可以在 Safari 浏览器中看到这些标签页了
and now, I can get to them in Safari
就像之前的 Pages 文稿文件一样
Just like with the Pages document
小组里的每个人都自动拥有了这些标签页的访问权限
everyone in the group automatically has access
我能看到 Anne 和 Mindy 加入了这个标签组
I can see Anne and Mindy joining the tab group
我甚至可以在标签栏里看到大家正在看哪些标签页
and I can even see which tabs people are looking at right in the tab bar
看起来 Mindy 正在看皮划艇
Looks like Mindy is checking out kayaking
我又找到了一些来看看吧
Lopp: Found a few more. Check these out
当 Lopp 添加标签页时它们会立即出现
Craig: When Lopp adds tabs, they instantly appear
这样我们所有人都可以查看了
so we can all check them out
让我们来看看我们去年已经做过这个了
Let's see, we already did this last year
但是高空滑索看起来很酷
but ziplining looks cool!
这样吧各位让我们总结一下
All right, team, let's wrap this up
把最新的想法添加到文档里
and update our document with the latest ideas
看起来 Anne 正在更新文本
Looks like Anne is updating the text
而 Mindy 刚刚添加了一张图片
and Mindy just dropped in an image
这样我们就都准备好了
so we're all set
那么以上就是对在 iPadOS 16 中
So that's a quick look at some of the new ways
用协作功能工作的简介
you can work together with collaboration with iPadOS 16
除了 Pages 文稿和 Safari 浏览器
In addition to Pages and Safari
这些新的协作功能还可以和其他各种 app 一起使用
these new collaboration features will work with a variety of apps
比如备忘录和 Keynote 讲演
like Notes and Keynote
而对于开发者则会有新的 API 来让他们在自己的 app 中集成协作
And for developers, there's a new API to integrate collaboration in their apps
这些功能也会添加到 iOS 和 macOS
and these features will also be coming to iOS and macOS
当然在实时协作时
Of course, when you're collaborating live
有时你会需要一个不受限的空间
sometimes you want a space where you can brainstorm
用来头脑风暴捕捉灵感
and capture ideas as they strike
所以今天就让你先睹为快一个叫做 Freeform 的全新 app
So today, we're giving you a sneak peek at a brand-new app called Freeform
它会在今年晚些时候发布
coming later this year
让 Elizabeth 为你详细介绍吧
To tell you all about it, here's Elizabeth
我们有各种各样的精彩方式来达成协作
Elizabeth Reid: We have so many great ways to collaborate
但是直到今日你还是没有一个空间可以用来工作
but up until now, you didn't have a space to work in
用来开展小组会议规划项目
a place for group sessions, project planning
家庭装修或者完成学校作业等等
home renovations, or school projects
现在即使你正在 FaceTime 通话中
Now, you can be on a FaceTime call
只要轻点一下
and with a tap, you're all collaborating live on a Freeform board
你就可以在一个 Freeform board 中开始实时合作了
你可以在画板上添加几乎任何东西
You can add almost anything to a board
它非常适合用来头脑风暴会议记笔记、共享文件
It's perfect for brainstorming sessions, jotting down notes
或是和其他人一起创建图表
sharing files, or even creating diagrams with others
它非常灵活多变唯一限制它的只有你的想象力
It's flexible, limited only by your imagination
当别人写下他们想法的时候
As others begin adding their thoughts
你可以看到他们的光标在实时向你展示他们工作的位置
you can see their live cursors showing you right where they're working
如果有人在用 Freeform 的另一部分
And if someone is in another part of Freeform
你只要轻点就可以直接跳转到他们在画板上的位置了
you can just tap to jump straight to where they are on the board
而如果你需要更多空间只需要用手指触控屏幕来移动就可以了
And any time you need more space, move around simply using touch
或者可以通过手指缩放专注在真正重要的事情上
or focus on what's really important with a pinch
当然画布还配备了完整的绘画工具
Of course, with a full complement of drawing tools
用 Apple Pencil 就可以随心所欲画草图记笔记
you can sketch or write a note anywhere you'd like with Apple Pencil
iPad 上有无数用来创作的强大工具
And with all the powerful tools to create content on iPad
而 Freeform 则是把它们整合在一起的地方
Freeform is a great place to pull it all together
你可以把包括照片、视频、音频
including photos, video, audio
文档、PDF 文件、网页链接在内的
documents, PDFs, web links
任何你需要的东西放到画板上
pretty much anything you need to work with can be brought onto your board
而且你还可以直接预览甚至可以预览多页文档
And you can preview right in line, including multipage documents
和高分辨率视频
and high-resolution videos
这些工具可以为你提供所需要的一切
giving you everything you need
让你的想法触手可及
to bring your ideas to life right at your fingertips
这就是 Freeform 的简介
And that's a sneak peek at Freeform
交回给你 Craig
Back to you, Craig
Freeform 非常适合用来
Craig: Freeform is going to be a great way
与他人集思广益
to brainstorm your ideas with others
而且今年晚些时候我们要把它
and we're building it right into iPadOS
引入 iPadOS、macOS 还有 iOS
macOS, and iOS later this year
当然 iPad 的多用性意味着
Of course, the versatility of iPad means you can seamlessly move
你可以让工作和游戏无缝衔接
from being productive to gaming
凭借它绚丽的显示屏和各种内置传感器
With its stunning display, built-in sensors
还有对常用游戏手柄的支持
and support for your favorite game controller
iPad 带来了绝佳的游戏体验
iPad provides a great gaming experience
并且 M1 芯片带来了超高图形处理性能
And the M1 chip delivers high-performance graphics
为 Divinity Original Sin 2 这样的沉浸式游戏提供支持
enabling immersive games like Divinity: Original Sin 2
在 iPadOS 16 中我们还带来了对游戏的更新
In iPadOS 16, we have some great updates to gaming
首先 Metal 3 为 iPad 带来了
starting with Metal 3
我们之前在 macOS 中讲到的相同的 MetalFX 上采样技术
which brings the same MetalFX upscaling
和快速资源加载 API
and fast resource loading API to iPad that we talked about earlier with macOS
还有新的 API
There's also a new API
可以让游戏在后台下载大型资源
that lets games download large assets in the background
让你在下载的过程中也能执行多项任务
enabling you to multitask while the download completes
在 iPad 上游戏的另一个好处就是让我们共享精彩
Another important aspect to gaming on iPad is how it brings us together
成千上万的游戏都用 Game Center
Tens of thousands of games use Game Center to help us
来帮助我们和朋友一起游戏或者比拼
play with our friends or compete against each other
使用你的 Game Center 资料就无需创建新账户
It's easy to jump right in and play without creating a new account
直接进入游戏
using your Game Center profile
你可以找到一起玩的朋友在排行榜上比拼分数
You can find friends to play with, compare scores on leaderboards
并通过成就跟踪进度
and track progress through achievements
现在我们在 Game Center 主页添加了活动功能
And now, we're bringing Activity to the Game Center dashboard
你可以看到你的朋友正在玩什么游戏他们取得了哪些成就
You can see what your friends are playing, highlights of their achievements
甚至可以了解他们什么时候分数超过了你
and even find out when they beat your high score
这样你就会知道是时候把你的游戏提高到新的水准
so you know when it's time to take your game to the next level
重新占领鳌头了
and get back on top
所有这些活动都会出现在你的 Game Center 资料上
And all of this activity appears on your Game Center profile
Game Center 一直都支持实时联机游戏
Game Center has always supported playing together in real time
现在同播共享让加入游戏开始联机变得非常容易
Now, SharePlay makes it simple to join and play
在 Game Center 的多人游戏中
In a multiplayer game using Game Center
只要开启同播共享就可以邀请你的朋友来加入
just start a SharePlay session and bring your friends right in
这些 Game Center 的新功能
These new Game Center features will be coming to an update
将于今年的晚些时候在 iPadOS 16 的更新中出现
to iPadOS 16 later this year
我们也会把它引入 iOS 和 macOS 里
and we're also bringing them to iOS and macOS
iPad 的多用性让它能用来做各种各样的事
The versatility of iPad makes it great for so many things
而其中有很大一部分都是 app 做到的
and a big part of that is apps
今年我们将持续努力让 iPad 上的 app
This year, we're continuing our work to make iPad apps more capable
更符合桌面级 app 的要求
with desktop-class apps
虽然许多 iPad 上的 app 都起源于 iOS
While many iPad apps have their origins in iOS
而这些年来很多 app 纷纷推出了各种独特功能
over the years, they've taken on their own unique capabilities
专门针对 iPad 更大的显示屏进行了优化适配
optimized for the iPad's larger display
在 iPadOS 16 中我们针对整个系统
In iPadOS 16, we scoured the entire system
进行了全面的优化
adding enhancements across the board
从系统元素到交互方式
from system elements and interactions
还有你在 Mac 上使用过并希望在 iPad 上实现的新功能
to new features you use on Mac and want on iPad
我要强调其中的几点
Let me highlight a few of them
跨系统撤销/重做
Undo/redo across the system
日历中的可用性视图
availability view in Calendar
在联系人中查找和合并名片还有创建列表
find and merge cards and create lists in Contacts
我们还对文件 app 进行了重大更新
and we have a big update to Files
增加了许多大家一直希望的功能
with some of the most requested features
比如更改文件扩展名
such as the ability to change file extensions
查看文件夹大小等
view folder size, and more
我们还添加了许多系统级功能为各种 app 都带来了优化体验
We've also added system-wide features that deliver improvements across apps
首先就是经过重新设计的
starting with a redesigned find and replace experience
查找和替换
that works in-line
在文件、Pages 文稿 Keynote 讲演等 app 的文档菜单中
A document menu in apps like Files, Pages, and Keynote
显示了常见的操作
that reveals common actions you may want to take
如复制、重命名、导出和打印
such as duplicate, rename, export, and print
并且在 iPadOS 中首次实现了可定制的工具栏
And for the first time ever, customizable toolbars in iPadOS
这样你就可以自由添加对你最重要的工具
so you can add the tools that matter to you most
而对于开发人员我们提供了一系列 API
And for developers, we've created new APIs
这样他们就能在自己的 app 中创建这些功能了
so they can build these capabilities right into their own apps
这些功能可以让你更高效
These features will help you be more productive
还有一个来自 Mac 的功能
And we have another feature for Mac that will be great
非常适合创意人士在 iPad 上使用
for creative pros on iPad
那就是参考颜色
And that is reference color
我们最新的 12.9 英寸 iPad Pro 配备了 Liquid 视网膜 XDR 显示屏
The Liquid Retina XDR display in our latest 12.9-inch iPad Pro
适合专业的色彩工作流程使用
is great for professional color workflows
而在 iPadOS 16 我们引入了参考模式
And with iPadOS 16, we're introducing Reference Mode
其色彩标准可用在各类工作流中例如一起讨论、审批
which meets the color requirements in workflows like review and approve
校色、色彩合成等
color grading, and compositing
在这些工作流程中准确的色彩和统一的图像质量非常重要
where accurate colors and consistent image quality are critical
因此不管你是想要把 iPad Pro 作为独立设备使用
So whether you prefer using iPad Pro as a standalone device
还是使用随航功能让 iPad 作为第二台显示器
or as a second display with Sidecar
参考模式都能为你的专业设备
Reference Mode provides a consistent reference workflow
提供统一的参考工作流程
across your pro devices
让 iPad Pro 成为创意人士不可或缺的工具
making iPad Pro an indispensable tool for creative professionals
现在我想要来聊聊最新的 iPad Pro 和 iPad Air 中
Now, I want to turn our attention to a set of features
M1 芯片的性能所带来的一系列功能
enabled by the performance of the M1 chip
in our latest iPad Pro and iPad Air
这些功能是为那些将 iPad 的多用性发挥到极致的人准备的
Features for people who push the versatility of iPad to the limit
专业人士总会希望有更多工作空间
Pros are always wanting more space to work with
所以我们增加了一个新的显示缩放设置
so we're adding a new display scaling setting
它可以让你增加显示器的像素密度
which allows you to increase the pixel density of the display
这样你就可以在 app 中查看更多内容
so you can view more in your apps
这点在使用分屏浏览的时候特别有用
which is particularly helpful when using Split View
我们还希望帮助你在 app 中做更多事情
We also want to enable you to do more in apps
我们最新的 iPad Air 和 iPad Pro
Our latest iPad Air and iPad Pro
配备了大量超快内存和储存空间
come with a ton of ultra-fast memory and storage
iPadOS 16 增加了对虚拟内存交换的支持
iPadOS 16 adds support for virtual memory swap
这意味着你的 iPad 储存空间
meaning your iPad storage can be used
可以用来扩展所有 app 的可用内存
to expand the available memory for all apps
而且还能为要求最高的 app 提供高达 16GB 的内存
and delivers up to 16 GB of memory to the most demanding apps
有了显示缩放和虚拟内存交换等技术
With technologies like display scaling and virtual memory swap
我们就为在用户体验方面实现飞跃奠定了基础
we have the foundation for a big leap forward in user experience
它可以改变我们的专业用户在 iPad 上工作的方式
one that can change how our Pro users get work done on iPad
所以我们把台前调度
So we're bringing Stage Manager
就是你刚刚在 macOS 上看到的最新窗口系统
our latest windowing system that you just saw in macOS, to iPadOS
引入到了 iPadOS
台前调度把 iPad 上的多任务处理提升到了一个全新的水平
Stage Manager takes multitasking on iPad to a whole new level
让它变得更加快捷也解锁了对外接显示器的全面支持
by making it more nimble and unlocking full external display support
我现在就展示给你们看
I'd like to show it to you now
迄今在 iPad 上当你使用 app 的时候
Today on iPad, when you use apps
它们会以我们熟悉的全屏方式打开
you get the full screen experience that we're all familiar with
就像这里的照片一样
like in Photos here
激活台前调度之后我现在就可以调整窗口的大小
With Stage Manager activated, I can now resize windows
这为在 iPad 上使用 app 提供了一种强大的新方式
exposing a powerful new way to work with apps on iPad
程序坞也触手可及所以我可以轻松访问所有的 app
And the Dock is visible, so I can easily get to all my apps
让我们打开音乐 app
Let's open Music
你会注意到所有我最近用过的 app 都显示在左边
You'll notice that all my recently used apps appear on the left
在它们之间可以快速切换
so switching between them is really fast
台前调度为我提供了出色的全新布局功能
And Stage Manager gives me powerful new layout capabilities
让我可以创造出我理想的工作空间
to create my ideal workspace
在 iPad 上我第一次可以在重叠窗口中工作
For the first time on iPad, I can work with overlapping windows
我现在要把信息 app 拖到日历 app 旁边
I'm gonna drag Messages alongside Calendar here
而当我把信息 app 拖到屏幕中间时
and Stage Manager automatically moves Calendar gently off to the side
台前调度会自动把日历轻轻移动到旁边
as I bring it to the stage
如果我把信息 app 移动到屏幕左边
And if I move Messages to the left
台前调度也会自动为日历 app 改变位置
Stage Manager repositions Calendar for me automatically
而且就像你之前看过的那样我可以调整窗口的大小
And like you saw earlier, I can resize windows
按照我想要的方式安排所有内容
and arrange everything just the way I want
而当我把 iPad 连接到外接显示器的时候
And it gets even better
这些功能会更强大
when I plug my iPad into an external display
我的墙纸可以完美地填充整个屏幕
My wallpaper beautifully fills the entire display
我也可以把光标从 iPad 移动到屏幕上
and I can move my cursor to it from my iPad
我在这个显示屏上也可以访问程序坞现在让我们打开 Keynote 讲演
I have the Dock here too, so let's go ahead and launch Keynote
这时我就在一个更大的空间内
When I do, I once again enter Stage Manager
再次进入了台前调度
now on an even bigger canvas
这些额外的屏幕空间
All of that additional screen real estate is so useful
在用 Keynote 处理演示文稿的时候非常有用
when working on a presentation in Keynote
而且当你需要用一组 app 来工作的时候它也能完美应对
And it's amazing when you're working with a set of apps
我可以创建有三个甚至四个窗口的组
I can create groups of three and even four windows
它的功能非常强大
This is just incredibly powerful
结合我的 iPad 和外接显示器
Between my iPad and my external display
我最多可以同时使用 8 个 app
I can have up to eight apps running onscreen simultaneously
而且我还可以利用这些显示器的独特功能
And I can take advantage of the unique capabilities of each of these displays
例如我正在处理这个 Keynote 演讲文档
For instance, I'm working on this Keynote document
而这时我想添加一张用 Procreate 画的图
and I want to add a drawing from Procreate
在我的 iPad 上
here on my iPad
我可以用 Apple Pencil 来为我的绘图
I can use Apple Pencil to add a finishing touch
完成最后的点睛之笔
to my drawing
现在我可以回到图库
And now I can jump back into the gallery
把显示器里的绘图拖过来直接放进我的演示文稿中了
and then drag and drop across displays and into my deck
以上就是对台前调度的简短介绍
And that's a quick look at Stage Manager
它带来了一种全新的多任务处理方式提供多个窗口的重叠
It's an entirely new way to multitask with multiple overlapping windows
灵活的窗口设定快速的 app 切换
flexible window sets, fast app switching
以及对外接显示器的全面支持
and full external display support
这就是 iPadOS 16
And that's iPadOS 16
这次重大发布为许多内置 app 带来了超棒的更新
a big release with exciting updates to many of the built-in apps;
为 iPad 引入了天气 app
Weather app comes to iPad
带来了进行协作和提供生产力的新方式
new ways to collaborate and be productive
为专业级用户带来了包括台前调度在内的众多新功能
great features for pro users, including Stage Manager
当然还有很多
and so much more
现在回到 Tim
Now, back to Tim
感谢 Craig
Tim: Thank you, Craig
感谢我们所有的演讲者
And thanks to all of our presenters
这真是激动人心的一天！
What an exciting day of announcements!
我们推出了重新设计过的全新 MacBook Air
We introduced the all-new, redesigned MacBook Air
它拥有超薄机身 Liquid 视网膜显示屏
with its super-thin enclosure, Liquid Retina display
MagSafe 和精美的新外观
MagSafe, beautiful new finishes
并由我们新一代 Apple 芯片 M2 驱动
and supercharged by M2
our next generation of Apple Silicon
还有同样由 M2 芯片驱动的
Along with a powerful new 13-inch MacBook Pro
强大的全新 13 英寸 MacBook Pro
also supercharged by M2
当然还有我们各大软件平台的进步带来各种令人惊喜的新方式
And we pushed our software platforms forward in some incredible new ways
同时推出的各种新特性和功能来帮助我们的开发者们大展身手
Introducing features and capabilities that will enable our developers
最终为我们的用户带来奇妙的新体验
to do amazing work and provide our users with exciting new experiences
我们的操作系统将于今天以开发者 Beta 版的形式发布
Our OS releases will be available as developer betas today
并在下个月推出 Public Beta
and each of them will have a public beta next month
所有这些操作系统更新都会在今年秋天提供给我们的用户
All of these OS releases will be available to our users this fall
我相信我们这些优秀的产品和创新的平台
I'm confident that our incredible products and innovative platforms
将会激励开发者们打造出他们的杰作
will inspire developers to do the very best work of their lives
并最终赋能我们所有人实现各种精彩
enabling all of us to do even more amazing things
我们希望你喜欢今天的活动
We hope you enjoyed today's event
接下来的一周将精彩纷呈
and we have a huge week ahead
我们会带来全面的线上体验
We will be offering a comprehensive online experience
从 Platform State of the Union 开始
starting with a Platform State of the Union
开发者们可以更深入了解我们最新的发布
for those developers who want take a deeper dive into our announcements
而且还会有超过 175 场讲座
And there will be more than 175 sessions
和与 Apple 工程师的一对一开发者实验室
as well as one-on-one labs with Apple engineers
以及数字聊天室
and digital lounges
所有这些活动都为我们的开发者免费提供
All of this is available for free to all our developers
让大家在 WWDC 收获更多
to help them get the most out of the conference
感谢大家的参与希望我们的 WWDC 取得圆满成功！
Thank you for joining us, and let's have a great WWDC!
♪♪
制作期间的健康与安全事项
为讲者及演职人员提供每日健康筛查和检测
严格保持社交距离并积极监督遵守情况
除了正在被拍摄的讲者及参演人员外所有人均获发并佩戴了口罩
♪♪
拍摄过程中现场只有讲者及演职人员
当有多名讲者或演职人员在同一现场时按需求采取了额外措施
制作场地均定期进行彻底消毒
♪♪
Apple 活动 Apple Park  Cupertino